We've finally got our stolen coords back!
Isn't that great?!
C'mon! Let's snap!
Okay.
ENTERTAINMENT
FIRST LOOK
This is the entertainment news.
Internationally famous movie star
and winner of the title of "Ideal Prince",
Shikyouin Hibiki, has revealed she's actually a girl.
Shikyouin Hibiki's
Splendid Everyday Life
Hibiki has made her idol début in PriPara,
the female-only idol themeworld.
For fans of hers in EuroPara, Pamerica, Aprica, Pasia,
and others around the world, this has come as a big shock.
Great!
Keep it coming!
That's great, Hibiki!
I've taken the Tears of Yuriya as promised!
Fare thee well, gentlemen!
And cut!
Hibiki!
A word for your fans!
Why have you been pretending to be a man?
Are you really a female?
Why did you make your PriPara début now?
My PriPara début?
You've got it backwards.
PriPara has finally met Shikyouin Hibiki.
You'll understand once I finish dyeing Pripara in my color.
And that will be its revolution.
SEARCH TERM RANKING
RANK   LAST TIME                                                   KEYWORD
15th                    Shikyouin Hibiki
UNRANKED                                                             Hibiki girl
UNRANKED                                                              Vacation
4th   UNRANKED                                Shikyouin
5th   UNRANKED                               Hibiki rose
6th   UNRANKED              Crimes committed by Phantom Thief Genius
This is the third straight day Shikyouin Hibiki has
been at the top of the search team rankings.
Why is someone like her so popular?!
I'm way more charming!
It's probably because she's a huge celebrity.
She also has a detailed online profile.
Shikyouin Hibiki
She made her début as a male model at seven years old.
And ever since then,
she's been described as a prodigy young actor...
...and has come to be known as the "Ideal Prince".
So she's been playing a boy for a long time.
But why would she do that if she's a girl?
When she made her début,
Hibiki revealed she is Phantom Thief Genius...
and indicated that her intention is to
change the face of PriPara to fit her ideals.
In later comments,
she mentioned that everything depends on the
outcome of the upcoming Winter Dream Idol GrandPrix.
If the team Hibiki puts together happens to win,
all of her previous crimes will be overlooked,
and there's a chance she'll be allowed to dictate the future of PriPara's policies.
No way!
We're gonna win and make her beg for forgiveness!
Yeah!
There's no way we'll lose!
We got it!
But her performance was really impressive.
And so were her wings.
We certainly made a rash decision when she challenged us,
but...
We can still win.
Huh?
Everyone who Airy Changed
at the Dream Theatre gained wings.
And...
And?!
...we have Manaka's burning idiot power.
Whenever we're in peril,
she has a strange power that manifests.
Back then, and then...
I'm sure I saw that power.
H-Huh?
You sure?
I am.
And on top of that, we're hard working.
Einstein once said
"Genius is 1% talent and 99% percent hard work".
If they come at us with a team of prodigies,
we'll be fine with an average team that's hard working!
Yeah!
Capisce!
Wait.
Actually, where are Sophy and Sion?
I'm not sure.
Didn't they have something come up?
Please pardon my appearance.
There's a rather boring event I must attend shortly.
Why did you call us here?
Yeah?
As I'm sure you know,
I'm forming a team of prodigies for the upcoming WinDrea.
Houjou Sophy, Toudou Sion,
I am formally inviting you to join my team.
The looks on your faces tell me
you're unsure how to answer.
But it's quite simple, if you ask me.
You need only be honest with yourselves.
What?
You saw my performance, didn't you?
And the radiance of my wings as I flew?
I'm sure you must have thought
"I want to put on a flying performance like her".
How do you know that?
A prodigy knows a prodigy when she sees one.
Being that we're prodigies, a reaction unlike anything seen before will take place as we perform together.
And then we'll be able to witness a scene
unlike anything anyone has ever seen.
A scene no one has seen before?
I understand what you're talking about.
But your words are meaningless.
I've decided to do things my way.
That's fine.
I'm sure you'll join me eventually.
What did you think?
Something like...
Pushuu...
I'm swimming along, thinking I'm a jellyfish,
but then she says "you are a mushroom",
even though I'm a jellyfish.
Then are cloud ear mushrooms jellyfish? Or mushrooms?
That kind of feeling.
I can't relate.
Phantom Thief Genius' arrest is entirely dependent
upon the outcome of the WinDrea.
It's unfortunate we couldn't accomplish
anything as the PriPara Police.
As of today, the special investigation team
is being disbanded.
Degas!
How deeply regrettable-da Vinci!
I'll be returning to my normal job
of supporting the idols here.
As for Sir Ham and the rest of you,
please continue to protect the peace within this town as part of the PriPara Police.
Roger!
Pan!
Here's your SummerDrea ticket.
Thanks.
I'm glad you're doing better than I expected.
It must have been quite a shock to find out
the guy she liked is actually a girl.
Get better soon so we can perform together again!
I will!
All right, see you later.
How are you doing, Fuwari-tori?
Toriko.
It was quite the shock, wasn't it-tori?
You ended up getting hurt all because Toriko's your manager-tori!
That means Toriko is a terrible manager-tori!
Don't worry.
I love you, Toriko.
Then please listen to Toriko's request-tori!
Please go outside and get a breath of fresh air soon-tori!
Okay.
Andou?
I have a half-hour gap in my schedule.
Is my horse ready?
My apologies, Master Hibiki.
Maxi actually jumped over the
high school riding club's fence...
Maxi!
Did you come to see me?
I'm so glad I came outside.
Maxi.
I told you not to come here, did I not?
Come, we're going back.
Hibiki, wait.
I'm, um... shocked.
Not only are you Phantom Thief Genius,
but you're also a girl.
I understand you even less now.
You've told me so much,
but which parts were the truth and which were lies?
As if I'd ever lie to you.
Huh?
Fuwari, I was only ever...
...in love with you.
Did you really think I was serious?
What?!
To me, a performance like this is a mere everyday thing.
Fooling a backwater country girl
from the Palps is but a simple task.
Would you like me to whisper
more passionate words in your ear?
How could she...
You're in bed again-tori?!
This is all Toriko's fault-tori!
Okonomiyaki
Ninja
Monja
Miss Hibiki, are you planning on continuing
your career as a girl from here on out?
Surprise Interview
Shikyouin Hibiki
I'll continue doing things my own way,
just as I always have.
I heard that you're playing the role of a girl
dressed as a guy in your next movie.
We've already begun rehearsals.
I hope all of you enjoy it.
Surprise Interview
Shikyouin Hibiki
For crying out loud!
I've heard enough about Hibiki!
Why aren't they going on about
Dorothy this and Dorothy that?!
Dorothy, I have a favor I'd like to ask of you...
Huh?
Miss Shikyouin Hibiki
Oh, Miss Hibiki!
You're a dashing heartthrob as always!
Ah, this time you're a Knight of Persailles.
Who would have thought this would
be the perfect movie for you right now.
You're going to end up with even more fans, aren't you?!
Excuse me.
It seems we'll start late as our heroine,
Ms. Barazono Yuri's, flight has been delayed about an hour.
Huh?!
I don't care if she's a Parademy Award winner,
she's got a lot of nerve, making Hibiki wait like this.
Ouch!
I'm sorry!
Miss Hibiki, please be a darling and wait an hour.
I wait for no one.
Reschedule the rehearsal for another day.
Miss Hibiki, wait!
Why not?!
Lemme go!
Shut it!
Dorothy West,
and her younger brother, Reona West...
What are they planning?
Darn!
And here I thought we could sneak in and surprise you.
Do you know these people, Miss Shikyouin?
No. Please toss them out.
Huh? That's not very nice, Gigi.
Um...
Why do you present as a guy?
That's all I want to know.
I just wanted to see what you're usually like.
Reona West...
It's said that the PriPara goddesses
have made exception for this idol.
He doesn't look the slightest bit masculine.
Though, he did chase my smash once.
Cheer up, Miss Hibiki.
The program after this needs you, too.
Why not.
Great!
However, it'd be quite boring to just wait around.
Huh?
Why don't we use a stand-in until my co-star arrives?
Huh? A stand-in?
Her!
Huh?!
What?!
I'll answer your question if you'll serve as our stand-in.
I'll do it.
As I mentioned earlier,
this rehearsal is just for practice and to check lighting,
so you just need to match the mood.
Now let's have some fun.
Okay, "Knight of Persailles" act 2, scene 2,
the scene where our knight rescues the princess from the pirate ship.
Action!
Knight of Persailles
Why am I dressed like this?!
Why am I the pirate?!
I'm way too cute to be the pirate!
Cut it out! Stop!
Action!
Princess, I am glad you're safe!
I've traveled these stormy seas
upon the call to rescue you!
I shan't let you pass into the hands of these pirates!
Wh-Why have you come?
Flee while you still can!
And leave you in this place?!
I would rather throw myself to the sea!
And now the pirate's line!
Let's see...
The princess is escaping!
Don't let her get away!
...what's with this line?!
Bring me the director and screenwriter!
We're out of time!
Here, take my hand!
I'm not coming with you...
Because I know the truth.
Your true side... Your insincere love.
The words you whisper with those lips...
That hand you gently extend to me...
I finally understand that they're all a lie!
That female stand in is pretty good.
She's pretty, too.
All right! Your line, pirate!
The princess is escaping!
Don't let her get away!
You're actually a girl, aren't you?
Yet, why is it that you dress like that?
Why, you ask?
The world is made of lies and deceit, you see.
So what, pray tell, is the problem?
What?
H-Huh?
"Due to family circumstances, I was raised as a man"...
...is the line she should have said.
And you?
Me?!
What about yourself?
This...
This is who I am!
I see.
That's not her line!
You good with this?
Shut it!
I've come up with a great idea!
Even if I must turn the heavens against me,
I will do anything to protect you!
Even if I must sacrifice myself for you, princess!
What do you think you're doing to Reona?!
Dorothy!
Hey, don't I have a cannon or something?!
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Let's get out of here, Reona.
I can't handle this jerk any longer—
Ms. Barazono has arrived!
That hurt! You moron!
Thanks for coming with me, Dorothy.
I thought Hibiki and I were the same,
but it seems we have some differences.
Similar how?!
You're nowhere near as insufferable as her!
She's just naturally disagreeable!
That fraud!
Please scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your coord.
Coord change, start!
An aristocratic vampire's coord must
be made up of chic, dark colors!
It looks exquisite, doesn't it?
Vampire Rose Coord!
With her début concert,
Hibiki was ranked a Celebrity Idol in Top Rank,
and became the highest ranking idol in PriPara!
Please look forward to another concert from this prodigy!
You there, within your powerful yet weak-willed heart,
kimi hakanaku mo tsuyoi
Find yourself spurred by revolution
sono kokoro ni ima kakumei nosetara
You there, heed now the future
kimi tomadowazu furuu
assured by my unerring nobility
seigi no naka ni aru mirai wo goran
Leave the past behind
kako wo wasurete
Unsuited to lipstick or ladylike apparel
doresu mo ruuju mo kanawanai
I am a perfect knight of beauty
rinjin mo kamigami mo urayamu
Envied by god and mortal alike
perfect beauty knight
Pure amore love - let it bloom ever magnificently
pure amore ai sakihokore utsukushii
A casablanca bursting open like raging magma
hana akaku takeru maguma kasaburanka ni
Amore, come here, I shall tell you now the truth
amore iza shinjitsu wo oshieyou
What is “love”?
ai suru to wa
Love is merely a fantasy for fools
oroka na shoudou
Yet it is by the love's whims that we two
shikashi bokura wa ai ga yue ni
Have been drawn here
koko ni iru
Making Drama, switch on!
Onward!
I will uphold it!
Sapphire revolution!
Pristine frenzy!
The wheels of revolution will not turn without sacrifice!
Now come here
oide
Airy Change!
Pure Amore Love - An eternally unfading bloom;
pure amore ai eien ni kawaranai
Gold Airy!
A casablanca with its thorns wrapped around your heart,
hana toge wo matotta mune no kasaburanka
Amore, ah! Avert not your eyes from the flower;
amore aa akai yori mo akai hana
its hue rivaling any shade of crimson
katsumoku se yo
This pristine frenzy is for you
junshin ranbu for you
Indeed, it's for the sake of love and these dreams
sou ai ga yue yume ga tame ni
That "I" am here
boku wa aru
Hibiki is yellow; Noble.
It fits her perfectly, doesn't it?
Amazing...
A scene never before seen...
I'll definitely take her down!
Don't worry.
We're all here with you, Dorothy.
That's right.
As long as we're together, we can't lose!
She may be pri formidable, but we've got this!
Yeah!
Next time
Whether to join Shikyouin's team or not...
A quick decision must be made!
What kind of scenery did she mean
by a scene no one has seen before?
The answer exists within me.
Go'ing My Way
Next time:
Go'ing My Way!