Let's begin the investigation-daVinci!
The clues are... here, and here!
Sakaida Kakiemon created the wood block printing revolution!
This was her face 10 years ago-daVinci!
Listen up, everyone-pri!
You'll lose out if you don't-pri!
You'll forget all about CelePara once you hear this!
Underground Pripara,
shortened as SubPara is now open-pri!
Come and see our amazing concerts-pri!
We'll be singing our hearts out!
You can only hear my amazing voice at SubPara!
Please come!
Won't you get told off for going there?
"Don't worry"
Lady Shikyouin said that outside of the Grand Prix,
we're allowed to do as we please.
That includes Sophy too.
Underground PriPara?
I heard SoLaMi SMILE, Dressing Pafé,
and Aromageddon will be there too!
Really?
But, CelePara is on right now.
True...
Y-You guys!
Don't get discouraged from the get go-pri!
You're right.
Pop, step, pri-ease come!
Huh?
Hanana?
I Became
an Underground Idol
Hanana?
H-Hello, Laala.
Hey-pri!
We're gonna do a concert at SubPara.
Pri-ease come!
S-Sure.
There you are!
Hanana, what are you doing?
I was about to head to SubPara.
Huh?
They only have measly tap water at SubPara.
What's your problem with tap water, huh?
Dorothy, relax.
Hurry up!
The CelePara concert is starting soon!
B-But...
Panet Jackson is performing today!
Cool! She's an internationally famous idol, right?
Hanana...
CelePara Shmele Para-pri!
Our performances are so much better-pri!
Please take one-pri!
Please come to SubPara!
Come see the special performance
of the future Divine Idol, Dorothy!
It'll be really fun!
What rank is today's guest?
A Top Class international idol.
This is what a performance should be.
A true talent shining,
with everyone else looking up to them.
Only a fool would leave a diamond in the rough.
It should be extracted,
and appreciated for its true value.
Through that, true emotions can be experienced.
Maho-chan.
Is something the matter?
Have you seen Gaaruru?
She was staying in my room,
but she's not there.
Gaaruru?
Don't bite her!
Ah, that little princess.
Come to SubPara-garu!
Gaaruru's gonna be performing!
Please come and see-garu!
Well, if it isn't the Monster Idol...
Garu?
Refrain from toiling so.
She's saying she wants to help!
Garu!
Gaaruru, won't you have a duel with us?
Garu?
Demon or Monster, who can hand out the most flyers?
Gaaruru won't lose-garu!
Okay? Ready, go!
The Cursed Banquet at SubPara is beginning!
It's the all-natural Monster Concert-garu!
Be my captive!
It's the SubPara counterattack!
The Great SubPara War-garu!
It'll be so much fun!
Please come visit us!
96, 97
Only 100 left for today...
No, I'll make 200-kuma!
I can't believe that...
...an elite manager like me has to make flyers underground-usa.
It'll be fine-nekon.
Just keep falling from grace.
Because then the only way is up,
isn't that wonderful-nekon?
She's right-kuma!
Even if Laala and Mirei can't perform in CelePara,
they can start again at SubPara-kuma!
My Aroma and Mikan can as well-nekon.
So can Dorothy and Reona, right-nekon?
You're right-usa...
Supporting the idols who are giving it their all,
that's a managers true duty.
Despite that,
I'm sitting here in self-pity. What am I doing-usa?!
How can I call myself an elite manager
when I'm sitting here moping-usa!?
A spring is at it's strongest when it's oppressed-usa!
It's almost time for a performance-usa!
Kuma, come help me set up-usa!
Hey!
You're the one who's helping me-kuma!
What a recovery. Boys are so simple-nekon...
But that's what I like about them-nekon.
As for someone else...
I stack another one...
for Fuwari...
And another one, for Fuwari.
And one more, for Fuwari.
What on earth has happened here-nekon?
It'd be best for you not to come!
It's the idol counterattack-garu!
It's the grand SubPara unveiling!
Please come!
Is SubPara around here?
Just follow Mikan!
Here it is!
Amazing! They're actually performing!
Only fifty?
Dorothy.
We only had fifty fans!
It's perfect!
Yeah-pri!
If we get more fans, we'll get more likes-pri!
Yeah.
So we just need to do more concerts,
and get more fans!
Laala!
Hanana!
You came!
I'm so glad.
Here's a "thank you" capisce!
Welcome to SubPara-pri!
Thanks!
I knew that I wanted to see
your shows and your friends' shows.
That's great!
We're gonna do plenty of them,
so be sure to come see us!
Laala!
I love SoLaMi SMILE!
Even though you can't enter the
Spring Dream, give it your all!
Capisce!
Pri!
It should be around here-daVinci...
It hasn't changed in ten years-daVinci!
There's a secret entrance if I remember-andt correctly.
It's over here-daVinci!
Ajimi.
Auguste Rodin!
The nostalgia!
All the tasty fruits like oranges and peaches
would grow in the summer!
Bunches of rare, southern fruit grew in the greenhouse!
I'd eat loads of them when I was little!
Hey, who are you?!
The gardener!
Long time, no see!
Who are you?
Fruit thief!
Are you here to steal fruit again?
I'll do that later.
Today, I just have something to ask you-daVinci.
Something to ask me?
This girl!
She used to live here-daVinci.
I used to call her "Li'l Curly",
but I never knew what her real name was-utrillo.
That's Lady Hibiki when she was younger.
You sure drew her well.
Hibiki!
I didn't know you saw her so much,
constantly being in and out.
How nostalgic.
She hasn't lived at this villa for the past ten years.
Ah, come to think of it,
she became the Mr. Universe Prince of the Year,
or something like that!
Bin-Gogh!
I knew Hibiki had to be Li'l Curly-daVinci!
How ominous.
Andou.
Ah, Master Hibiki, I should mention...
...it appears that an underground PriPara has been founded.
They're distributing flyers.
Ah, SubPara was it?
Leave them be.
They're no match for CelePara.
Idols will come to CelePara, I know it.
All is right with the world.
I'm sure Gaaruru must have gone to SubPara.
Gaaruru just keeps improving!
We'll take you to heaven!
No, hell!
With a pop and step, I've gotten all your hearts!
Everyone have fun — capisce!
Come join us, Hanana!
What? But...
I'm just a new experimental idol...
No problem!
This is SubPara; we're all friends, we're all idols!
Yeah!
But I don't have a manager...
Miss Hanana, please take him.
Hanana's solo debut concert.
Give it your all!
Hanana!
With a pop and a step, you're perfect-pri!
Thanks, Laala, everyone!
Thank you, SubPara!
Lovely
Hanana, you've ranked up from
Sparkling Experimental Idol...
to Novice Experimental Idol!
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Sparkling
Experimental
Idol
Novice
Experimental
Idol
Novice
Experimental
Idol
Congratulations.
That was so fun!
CelePara is the best!
Those are international idols for you!
Today's show was great. too!
It sure was!
It was so cool, I feel like I've had my fill!
That's what it really means to shine bright!
But... we're only watching...
She's right...
Only Top Class idols
and above can perform in CelePara.
Wanna go to SubPara?
Yeah!
We get to perform in SubPara!
Let's go!
Doesn't SubPara sound fun?
I really wanna show it to you, Fuwari!
There's been so many shows today.
Kuma, Usagi and even Nekonee...
have all been supporting us!
Toriko is her usual self,
but I'm sure she'll come around.
Although only a little,
even more fans and performers are coming...
and are having fun and performing!
Airy Change!
Gold Airy!
And Sion even got a Gold Airy!
We've gotta keep up with her!
See you later, Fuwari.
Please hurry on back.
Everyone's really giving it their all.
Ah, how I love the country air!
I'm fine just being Fuwari from the Palps!
Huh?
What's wrong?
Oh, Grandpa.
This one seems a little off... Their face is off-color.
Did you feed him something
out of the ordinary yesterday?
You did, didn't you?
Well, I didn't exactly "feed"...
But, some wine was left over, so we drank it.
For goodness sake.
It's mild dehydration.
This one, too.
Ah, that one drank beer.
Grandpa!
Hang in there. I'll be done with the medicine soon.
You're finally back to your old self.
When you came back from Parajuku,
you'd become a lot weaker.
I'd been wondering what happened to you.
Sorry for making you worry,
but I'm okay now.
Because I've realized that I'm Fuwari from the Palps.
PriPara just wasn't for me.
Ever since you were a child,
you could instantly tell if an animal was sick.
Just like now.
You can read the animals' emotions
just by looking at their faces.
Did those sharp eyes get blunt
with city life in Parajuku?
Grandpa?
Did you use those eyes to
look into the face of your prince,
when he told you it was all an act?
Or did you get complacent in happiness...
...when he told you you'd be a princess?
That was a lie, Hibiki's false form.
Fuwari, I was only ever in love with you.
That was a... lie...
I was so busy I couldn't talk to you today.
But once you've become an elegant princess,
I'll come sweep you off your feet.
These were also lies....
It was all a lie.
I've been lonely.
As I am known as a prince in this glamorous world,
all the women who approach me are nothing but shams.
That was true! She wasn't lying then!
You're so radiant, even the lobster is blushing!
That was a lie.
Your lack of a sentence ender sets the heart at ease.
That was really true.
What's your name?
Fuwari.
Midorikaze Fuwari.
Fuwari...
I've finally found you...
My princess...
That was the first truth.
Grandpa, I...
It seems you've found the answer.
I want to know more about Hibiki and what was true.
Also,
I have to make Toriko the blue bird of happiness.
It's obvious at this point that
Fuwari completely forgot about me-tori.
I'm used to it by now-tori.
Who will be performing today?
We're so much closer to the stage than at CelePara.
Wanna do a concert together?
Yeah! 100 people came today-kuma!
Now we can start counting in units of 100-nekon!
Making all those leaflets was worth it-usa!
Yeah! Let's do this, everyone!
We're all friends, we're all idols!
SubPara?
Everyone's having fun performing.
Won't you come, Maho-chan?
I have no interest in such subpar performances.
CelePara better suits you.