Got it, Falulu?
Make sure to eat your vegetables.
Don't be too picky. Make sre to eat both meat and fish,
and don't forget to drink milk!
There's no need to worry, Unicorn.
Call me if you come down with a cold!
Got it.
And-
Big Sis Falulu, keep your chin up!
Do your best to get in the Parade!
Make sure to message us!
You got it!
And also...
Yes?
Don't talk with people you don't know.
Don't go with people you don't know!
Understand?
Yes, Falulu understands.
Talk to you later, Unicorn.
Ah!
She hung up.
I'm already worried.
Hey, hey, Unicorn...
What is it?
We're missing one.
Missing...?
What?!
Falulu is going back to Parajuku's PriPara.
Their PriPara so much fun, and the people there are so nice.
Falulu can't wait!
Gaaruru can't wait.
Huh?!
Gaaruru.
Gaaruru?! Why?!
Gaaruru's also going to Parajuku's PriPara.
Gaaruru wants to see everyone again!
Sit down!
Please stay calm while we're in flight.
Shh!
Princess Falulu
Next is PriPara News.
The town's in an uproar over the return of the Legendary Idol, Falulu.
Instead of a brief return home, this time she'll be staying
at Parajuku's PriPara for an extended period.
We finally get to meet, Princess Falulu.
What are you doing, Gaaruru?!
Why'd you do that without telling anyone?!
Send her back as soon as you can, Falulu!
PriPara announcement:
We'll be arriving at Parajuku's PriPara momentarily.
Please shut off and stow any electronic devices.
We'll talk again later!
Contact me as soon—
Falulu's back!
Welcome back, Falulu!
Hold it right there-da Vinci!
Huh?
Are you renoir-eally Falulu?
Or are you a fake-daVinci?!
That hurts!
Gaaruru!
Oww-izumo!
It... doesn't hurt?
You came too, Gaaruru?!
Welcome back, Gaaruru!
Don't do that, Gaaruru!
Don't worry, she's just play biting.
Utamaro!
You're interfering with official police business-daVinci!
It looks like Gaaruru sure has grown.
It's quite something.
Vocal dolls grow quickly.
Falulu's back?!
From PriParis?
Really?
Falulu came back!
I have to go to her concert!
Me too!
Phantom Thief Genius?
Who's that?
He stole our SummDrea and AutDrea Coords!
I max won't let him get away with it!
I'll make sure to catch him-pri!
That's why PriPara is up in arms-usa.
We're sorry about the dreary mood-kuma.
It's okay.
Being able to see all of you again is more than enough.
Same for Gaaruru!
But you need to go back to PriParis, Gaaruru!
Why?
Unicorn's worried about you,
so you need to head back right away.
Hey, Falulu, wouldn't one day be okay?
Then one day, and only one day!
You better come back tomorrow, you hear!
Gaaruru!
Gaaru!
Isn't that great?
You know, I'm surprised that Unicorn sent Falulu by herself.
Yeah.
Go.
Falulu also wants to be in the Dream Parade,
so she asked Unicorn.
And Unicorn said, "go and do your best".
You've the makings of a good rival.
Go!
Let's do our best and get in the parade!
Yeah!
Falulu, it's time for your
welcome home ticket snapping event.
I want to snap with Lady Falulu!
The PriTicket snapping event is over here!
Any-dalí suspicious here?!
Find-alí them and arrest them-daVinci!
Here.
Thank you so much!
Hooray!
Aroma Prophecy Grimoire, chapter 56, verse 98:
"With this, thee shall become my servant"!
By that she means we're gonna be friends after this!
Thanks!
Here.
Thankies!
Thanks for the fortune telling back then.
Devi!
Gel!
Oh, little goats!
They're all fans of yours.
Thanks, little goats!
Here.
And you are?
Fuwari.
Midorikaze Fuwari.
The former Princess Scholarship student.
Guess she wasn't cut out for it.
Dorothy...
It's okay.
She's right.
It's Toriko's fault!
Toriko would be a poor excuse for a Nagoya chicken!
Astounding!
That was some adventure we had back then.
Back then everyone was like,
"we're gonna get the princess!"
Sorry about that.
No, it was all Toriko's fault!
Blame Toriko!
Now that I think about it, Genius showed up just after
Fuwari stepped down from being the princess...
Is it a coincidence-pri?
Nice to meet you, Fuwari.
Same to you, Falulu.
With this, we're all friends!
Yep.
After Falulu's done with her event,
why don't we all go get crêpes?
Yeah, that sounds wonderful.
Go!
Yeah!
Gaaruru's nibbling event is over here!
Gaalu!
Nibbling event?
What's that-usa?
Usa...
Actually, I could get addicted to this
exquisite painless and itchless play biting-usa.
It'd probably work on a stiff neck-kuma.
A little rougher...
Chew more! Chew more!
W-Wait!
Don't eat her.
Falulu, it's time for your interview.
So, Miss Falulu, you're
an extraordinary idol even in PriParis, yes?
That's because Falulu has Unicorn
and the Mini-Falulus supporting her!
You really do have quite
the impressive manager and friends.
Wow!
These daisies are beautiful.
The flower seeds you gave me turned out so beautiful!
I'm giving this one to you, Lady Falulu!
Thank you, Non.
Falulu!
Huh?
We're ready!
Let's get this glamor shoot under way.
Okay!
That concludes our photoshoot.
Nice working with you.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Nice work today!
PriPara announcement:
To all idols here, PriPara will soon be closing for the day.
Please be careful on your way home.
And enjoy your time in PriPara until then.
What? Already?!
We'll see them again tomorrow, Dorothy.
Let's head home in groups!
Everyone's heading home?
See you tomorrow.
Today was a lot of fun-pri!
See you later, Gaaruru.
Gaaru...
Why isn't Falulu heading home?
It's because she's a Vocal Doll.
This is Falulu's home.
Mikan's starving!
Let's head home and have dinner-devi!
Let's head in.
Gaaru.
♪I've already fallen in love with the world♪
I know!
I wonder what Kuma and Usagi are doing?
Oh? You came again today?
That makes me happy-nekon.
Of course-kuma!
This is paradise-usa!
I also want to drink with you two-nekon.
I'll have a new bottle of vegetable juice!
Same here!
Yes, a new bottle!
Here's your new bottle!
Falulu should probably head to bed about now
so she'll be ready for tomorrow.
Are Unicorn and the others doing okay?
No, not now!
Falulu decided she'd do her best,
even though she's alone!
Unicorn and the others are all rooting for Falulu.
Huh?
Ack!
Falulu's Non!
Falulu's Non...
Who's there?
Bonsoir, Princess.
Falulu, I've been wanting to meet you for so long.
Are you spending the evening alone?
In that case, if you would allow me to speak with you...
...I'd be honored.
Do you feel threatened?
It's like a dream come true.
For a Legendary Idol...
Don't talk with people you don't know.
I'm no one suspicious.
Just what game are we playing?
Here. Good as new.
Thank you!
Ah!
Falulu talked with someone she doesn't know.
So that's what it was.
But now we are no longer strangers, right?
Eh? Why do you say that?
Because it's already been five minutes since we met.
Here...
As thanks for fixing Falulu's Non.
Aren't those important to you?
Since you fixed something important,
Falulu should give you something important as thanks.
In that case, would you be willing to dance with me instead?
I am a mage who is protecting PriPara.
Protecting PriPara?
And I also desire...
...to be your one and only man.
A guy has made it into PriPara?
Because I'm a mage.
Really?
I've long been awaiting this moment...
The moment I get to meet you.
My, look how drunk you are.
Oh, what a beautiful moon-nekon.
Mr. Mage, what do you mean by protecting PriPara?
Those who currently partake in PriPara cannot fully control the true brilliance...
that has been lying mostly dormant in their coords.
I want to revolutionize PriPara,
and to do that, I must find five princesses
and create an idol team known as the Princess Team.
I wish to help PriPara grow into something more beautiful.
Princess Team...
And I need you to achieve that.
Please choose my team above all others,
Princess Falulu.
Falulu... a princess?
Falulu!
Huh?
No biting Falulu!
Gaaruru, stop!
Gaaruru, stop! Stay away from him.
Gaaruru will do her best to protect Big Sis Falulu!
Princess Falulu,
please keep this a secret between the two of us.
If you tell anyone, I will disappear.
Now then, it was a pleasure, Princess...
...and Little Princess.
Mr. Magician...
Gaaru...
It's finally time for your one year anniversary show, Falulu!
According to my calculations,
you're expected to jump up the rankings even further!
Good luck!
Capisce!
Um, Sophy...
On Falulu's balcony last night...
Not now. It's a secret.
Mmm.
Please scan the appropriate number of My Tickets for your coord.
Coord Change Start!
Falulu's coord has been upgraded to gold!
Along with the rainbow-colored shimmer
of her snowflake jewelery,
it's luxurious and dazzling.
Jewelery Princess Coord!
Hi, everyone! Falulu's home!
Welcome back, Falulu!
Falulu has returned to PriPara!
She loves this town, PriPara, and all of you!
We've been waiting for you!
We've missed you!
We love you, Falulu!
Lady Falulu!
The coord's true shine...
If Falulu has the power to bring it out,
she wants to show everyone!
And become a princess!
Making Drama Switch On!
Hop!
For all of you!
Tick Tock Flower!
Cyalume Change!
Falulu is the best!
L - O - V - E!
With all the likes she gathered, she has ranked up from Major Class's Widely Popular Idol...
...to Top Class's Nationally Renowned Idol.
Congratulations!
Everyone!
Falulu will become a princess!
It's a promise!
Falulu will be a princess?!
Unicorn will be there to pick you up when you land.
Falulu...
Hm?
Gaaruru doesn't like the magician.
Oh...
You're worried just like Unicorn is.
Gaaru...
Gaaruru!
See you again!
Gaaru...
Happy birthday, Laala!
Same to you, Nao!
Since we have the same birthday, let's celebrate together!
But you'll have a birthday concert, won't you?
I have a good idea!
Next time:
It's A Birthday Promise, Capisce!