Our exciting travels begin!
Such incredible scenery comes to life just as we take off.
It's been a long journey,
but we're gonna hang in there and go!
Fee as a bird;
people come and go as they please.
Look how everyone sports the latest fashions!
Let's kick it up a notch.
Even goddesses want to express themselves through song!
It's so much fun, it makes you smile!
We'll be traveling for a long, long time!
An opera singer?
Or maybe an artist?
Bonjour, idols!
Ours songs form an aurora in the sky
And this wonderful, ever-turning world combines into one.
Around! No matter where you go,
(Merry go!)
the whole world is friends
as our planet turns and turns —
the earth really is the greatest stage!
Around! (Merry go!)
When the Bell of Beginnings rings out...
(ring ring a bell)
we'll be smiling brightly in the parade!
(Around!)
Around the Pripa-land...
We'll go together!
I know...
The dreams we want to come true...
and all our ambitions...
each and every one of them will form a precious light.
C'mon, let's sing it one more time
The world is...
so wide,
so full of mysteries,
doesn't that make it beautiful and fun?
It's like our own theatre!
Around!
(Merry go!)
No matter where you go,
the whole world is friends...
Turning and turning,
our earth really is the greatest stage!
Around!
(Merry go!)
When the Bell of Beginnings rings out...
(ring ring a bell)
we'll be smiling brightly in the parade!
(Around!)
Around the Pripa-land!
Around the Pripa-land! (Around!)
(We'll go!)
Come with us!
Around the Pripa-land! (Around!)
Around the Pripa-land!
Let's go together!
Lalala...
(Around!)
Round round round! round! World!
Lalala...
(Around!)
Pretty Paradise World!