Good morning, My Prince.
Morning.
Hello to you too, goat.
Morning chores complete!
They still haven't contacted me about my coord,
so I suppose they're not done with it yet.
I can't wait for my debut!
Huh?
This box Toriko gave me makes sounds?
It's singing!
Fuwari's coord is done, but she's not picking up her phone.
I'm sure it's because she's ignoring me-tori!
That's it! Has to be!
That's got to be why!
Fuwari dances! Her first concert-tori!
Have you adjusted to school life yet, Midorikaze?
No, not quite.
This goat sure has become a big fan of yours.
Purity.
A place that hasn't been immersed in city life would be good for you.
No, I want to get used to the city.
I've found you!
Ack!
It's time for your princess lessons, Midorikaze!
Did you forget?
Oh! Already?
I'm sorry.
Princess lessons?
Hibiki is expecting big things from you.
However, it takes more than simply taking first in the PriPara Grand Prix to be a Princess.
It takes heart, technique, and physique!
That is to say a real princess is one who wholeheartedly wishes to achieve the pinnacle of femininity.
And in order to master this, princess lessons are required.
G-Good luck, Fuwari—
Hold it right there, Manaka.
Your shoes!
Walking on the backstay is
a classic example of bad manners.
Huh?
It appears I need to also thoroughly drill
some manners into you.
What...
I was just in a hurry this morning.
I normally wear them pro—
Paprika Academy rule number 1315:
Shoot!
"Even if you normally do it properly,
it doesn't mean you can walk on the backstay just because you're in a rush"!
Now then, let us begin your Princess lessons.
Okay.
Capisce!
Manaka!
Yes?
You're not allowed to use "capisce" during Princess lessons.
When responding, the two of you should use the proper "yes, ma'am".
Okay!
I said use "yes, ma'am"!
Ye...
Yes, ma'am.
Of course, ma'am.
We'd be glad to.
Yes, we'd be of course to.
We'll yes, ma'am.
We'll yes, we'd be ma'am, glad to.
Quit screwing around!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Good enough.
We'll start with this.
That's huge!
As a princess, you are expected to dance in high heels at a party.
Yes, Ma'am.
What's with you two?
You must stand up straight and elegantly!
Yes, Ma'am.
Stand up!
Now onto the tiara.
Being able to stay composed and maintain a cool smile even when wearing a heavy tiara...
Heavy!
...is a must for a Princess.
Ye... Ye...
Yes, Ma'am.
Now then, keep that posture as we start the lesson.
Eh?!
A PriPara Princess must worry about fashion above all else.
As such, we'll be going over some PriPara Trivia concerning coords.
Yes, Ma'am.
This China Rock Coord has a certain animal attached to it.
What is that animal?
Dressing Parfait wore that coord...
Let's see... what animal was it...?
Here's a hint: It's black and white.
I got it! It's a German cow.
Let's see, black and white... black and white...
A penguin! Or zebra?
The Suffolk is a species of sheep that's also black and white.
Those are all wrong!
Next hint:
We're continuing?!
It's a cute and popular animal.
Oh, I got it!
A tapir!
You hear cute and that's what you think!?
It is! All animals are cute!
We don't need that kind of thinking here!
This cute animal is...
And there it is!
A panda!
P-P-Panda!
Oh, that's right. A panda!
We don't have those in the Palps.
You're tiring.
But...!
When it comes to table manners,
a Princess who can use chopsticks is considered elegant.
These chopstick corrective casts will whip you into shape.
Torture? Isn't this torture?!
But it looks so good...
We shall partake in this wonderful food.
You must have good posture while eating.
Don't grasp your chopsticks!
Don't hold them in your mouth!
Don't bring the plate to your face!
Don't lose your chopsticks!
Even if food slips away, don't stab it!
Don't drop them!
Don't eat like a dog!
Pushuu~.
Once you're done eating, put your chopsticks on the chopstick rest.
Pushushuu~.
For crying out loud, you're a handful...
Huh?
Where's Midorikaze?!
She must have ran off!
Ouch.
High heels sure are rough on the feet.
Since I always ran around the mountains barefoot,
it'll take a while to get used to them.
Princess lessons are tougher than I expected.
But everyone came to see me off.
So I have to become a wonderful Princess.
I wonder what they're all doing.
I can't see the mountains or sky from here.
I wonder if everyone's doing well.
The young swallows in that nest,
I wonder if they've learned how to fly yet.
The small squirrels in the forest and the rabbits in the grasslands,
I wonder what they're doing right about now.
It's too soon to be homesick, Fuwari.
Midorikaze!
Where are you?!
It's Ookanda-sensei!
Uh-oh.
Are you unharmed?
P-Prince?!
It's Hibiki! How lucky!
I'm so jealous!
Okay, calm down.
To fly down like a goddess...
Just what part of the heavens are you from?
I'm sorry.
I thought I might be able to see the Palps if I climbed to the top of that tree.
Homesick, huh?
You are the one expected to win the Summer Dream Idol GranPrix and become the Dream Parade Princess,
in other words the ultimate Princess.
I knew you had the talent.
I look forward to your growth.
Hibiki!
Of course!
Hibiki is...!
J-Just where did she go?!
Did I go a bit overboard with the training?!
Huh?
Sorry I'm late.
I'll do my best with the Princess lessons!
Please be more strict with me, Sensei!
Huh?
Um...
Proper response!
Y-Yes, Ma'am.
Huh?
This song again!
Fuwari, that's a phone.
Phone?
Press that and then say "hello".
Hello! Hello!
H-Hello?
She finally answered-kuma!
Geez! Toriko has become quite a handful! It's troublesome-kuma!
After all, Toriko is unwanted-tori!
I should set off to the mascot graveyard-tori!
She completely lost her cool when you continually ignored her call.
I wasn't ignoring her.
I didn't know how to use a phone.
Tori?
I'm sorry I didn't think about it earlier, Toriko.
Toriko is my very, very precious manager.
Tori!
Thank tori!
I wanted to tell you right away-tori!
Your new brand is finally done-tori!
Hooray!
Bravo!
It's finally time for your début concert!
It's finally time for my début concert!
Cosmic hi!
Fuwari, thank you for waiting.
Congratulations on the start of a new brand.
New brand?
Here, try pulling on this ribbon.
Ribbon?
Coco Flower?
That's right!
I used Fuwari's image and created the new brand Coco Flower!
It's a brand that focuses on using natural materials while adding a novel arrangement to a cute country motif.
It has completely revolutionized the PriPara Fashion world!
Wow!
So cool!
And with that, CoCo Flower has opened a new store in PriPara!
Wow!
How wonderful!
Here's a PriTicket for the Tyrolean Fleur Coord.
I'm sorry it took so long.
Now go put everything you've got into your PriPara Change!
Thank you so much!
PriPara Change!
Complete!
It looks great on you!
You're super cute, Fuwari!
How lucky! I want a new brand, too!
Toriko.
That coord...
That coord looks perfect on you!
Thanks.
Mega-niisan should be sending you your debut song "This Song Tomareihi" soon.
And here it is!
Wow!
It's like your Birthday and Christmas presents have been rolled into one-tori!
Ah!
I'm sure after all this happiness something unfortunate will...
An assortment of Friday the 13th, your most unlucky day, and the armageddon will come-tori!
Lord have mercy on us. Please lord...
Don't worry. Calm down.
Mikan will take pudding and curry udon-nano!
Welcome!
To celebrate the opening of Coco Flower,
we will be selling pudding a la mode for a limited time!
Coco Flower?
What's that-nano?
It's a new brand created from Midorikaze Fuwari's image.
Aloma Prophecy Grimoire, chapter 259, section 5151:
"When the ultimate Princess appears,
the demon's grand power shall be demonstrated."
Fuwari, the one who currently basks in everyone's attention,
I shall do whatever it takes to draw thee into Alomagedon!
Then, Mikan will take 25 of those limited Coco Flower parfaits!
Hold on!
Gel?
I'm reluctant to part with the final note in my purse.
She's broke-nano.
Good luck with your début concert!
Make sure to put everything into your challenge.
Tension max!
Relax!
Look, Fuwari,
it's best to sing like you're trying to convey your feelings to someone.
If you do that, you can put more energy into it.
Convey my feelings... to someone...?
No! No! No!
I absolutely won't let you enter-tori!
Think about it-tori.
If you decide to do your début concert now,
things like make a misstep,
forget the lyrics,
accidentally drop the microphone,
and having the set fall down like a comedy skit are bound to happen-tori!
If that happens, there will be a storm of boos from the crowd.
You'll be heckled, eggs will be thrown, people will talk about you behind your back,
and you'll absolutely, completely, and undoubtedly regret it!
You sure are a noisy manager!
If you're too cowardly people will call you a chicken!
I am a chicken-tori!
You should just prepare an absolutely delicious meal of deep fried Toriko and vegetables...
...garnished with a potato and carrot glaze topped with tarter sauce-tori!
It'll be delicious-tori!
Y-You're super annoying!
Here, Fuwari.
Take this Cyalume Charm.
Thanks.
Hey, stop-pri.
No, don't do it-tori.
Toriko! You need to properly put in her entry-pri!
But it's been so long since Toriko has entered anyone she forgot how-tori!
Um...
Entry...
It's not possible-tori.
Of course it's impossible-tori.
Your entry has been accepted.
The leaf isn't needed.
Eh?!
Thanks.
Fuwari...
I'll be right back.
It'll be fine, Toriko.
I'll make it a complete success.
Cheer for me!
Good luck with your first concert!
Fuwari!
Go for it, Fuwari!
Congrats on your début!
Do your best!
You should do it more like that.
And go!
Take this!
Cut!
Making Drama Switch On!
Let's go!
A mysterious spring orchestra!
Cyalume Change!
That was the best "Yes, ma'am"!
Thank you!
Well, that wasn't too bad for her début.
Ah, Shikyouin's up, but I guess he's not ready yet..
The green glow indicates a natural type.
This is also the first time I've seen this colour.
She has also jumped up the rankings!
She made it all the way to Newbie Idol in one go!
Good job!
You blew it out of the park!
That concert was just like you-pri!
You have a voice that makes me feel like a child again.
Thanks!
I tried to show off the feelings of the Palps, my beloved home.
I was nervous, but I had a lot of fun!
I want to do it again!
Pri!
Yeah, let's do it!
Join SoLaMi Smile and aim to win the Summer Dream GranPrix with us!
Huh? What are you saying?
Fuwari is joining Dressing Parfait, right?
Right?
SoLaMi Smile!
Dressing Parfait!
SoLaMi!
Dressing!
SoLa!
Dres!
The team Fuwari will join,
Huh?
Toriko thinks it should be decided by her manager.
Tori?!
Yes?
H-Hibiki!
I watched Fuwari's concert.
Thank you for guiding her, Miss Gloria.
No, no, no! I did nothing!
However, let's change the song's Making Drama for her next concert.
Please make sure she's ready by the GranPrix.
This purple goat is...
A letter?
Congragulations on your debut concert.
Since you're a bit homesick,
I'll give you this Royal Imperial.
Truly yours, Hibiki.
Prince,
I'll make sure to become an elegant Princess.
Please wait for me.
Why?! Why?! Why?!
What do you mean we're prohibited from doing PriPara?
What? I didn't hear anything about this?
Ack! Principal Ookanda!
How delightful!
She's after us!
This is the same as a year ago!
We won't give up!
Well go to PriPara and perform no matter what!
Let's go, Lala!
Capisce!
PriPara is for everyone!
Next time:
PriPara Has Been Outlawed!
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!