If you're tired of these ordinary days
Heibon na hibi ni akichatta no nara
Dress up your heart and come play with everyone!
Kokoro kigaete asobi ni yukou minna de
With this happy music
Gokigen na Music
The future's calling from that new area, so let's be the first to arrive!
Kikoeru mirai no saishin area ichiban’nori shiyou
Your charm point is your wonderful smile
Charm point wa tobikiri no Smile
Gather up all your friends
Tomodachi minna atsumatte
If you ring the bell
Kane wo narashitara
Miracle Dreamer
Let's go find a dream that shines with rainbow colors
Nijiiro ni kagayaku yume wo mitsuke ni yukou
Once it sparkles and the excitement builds up
Kirakira tokimeitara
Just do as you like and enjoy yourself!
Omoi no mama tanoshinjae!
As long as I'm with you, I can go anywhere
Kimi to nara doko made mo yukeru yo
Let's start this never-ending story
Owaranai monogatari start shiyou
PriPara Dream Parade
If you're not sure whether to go for it or not
Okubyou to yuuki ga kenka shiteru nara
Come on over here quick 'cause we're waiting for you
Ima sugu koko e oide yo hora matteru
Not everyone can always get full points
Dare datte itsumo
So just be confident and go
Hyakuten bakari ja nai kara kimi mo jishin motte yukou
I’ve always dreamed
Zutto mae kara akogareteta
of standing upon the stage
Stage ni ima tatsu no sa
together with everyone
Minna to issho ni
Special Fever
Everybody has their own dream that shines with rainbow colors
Nijiiro ni kirameku yume wa hito sorezore
The choices are endless, after all
Yori dori midori dakara
Take one step forward and you’re on your way!
Ato ippo hora fumidashichae!
I don’t want to leave this as just a dream
Yume no mama owarasetakunai yo
Once you’ve decided on your very own, fly out
Original de kimetara tobidasou yo
PriPara Dream Parade
Let's go find a dream that shines with rainbow colors
Nijiiro ni kagayaku yume wo mitsuke ni yukou
Once it sparkles and the excitement builds up
Kirakira tokimeitara
Just do as you like and enjoy yourself!
Omoi no mama tanoshinjae!
As long as I'm with you, I can go anywhere
Kimi to nara doko made mo yukeru yo
Let's start this never-ending story
Owaranai monogatari start shiyou
PriPara Dream Parade