Laala! Fuwari! Do-Re-Sion!
Yeah!
Summer's here
Let's go on an adventure
There's a heap of things we want to do
That we want to know
We find a treasure map in the darkness
And we suddenly come across... a giant watermelon?!
Our hearts beat like crazy
At the familiar striped pattern
Dead or alive
What's happening up ahead?
There's no time to waste
Let's dive right in!
It's an unforgettable summer adventure
All right, everyone! We're all stocked up!
Let's make use of this happiness
Put up our arms, and push to the blue sky!
It's a surprising summer adventure!
Isn't it an awesome view?
It is!
This was well worth the thrill
Go for it! Hey hey! Let's dance!
Higher, higher, and even further up
Until you've reached the place you've been aiming for
Ring the bell as a signal
Ding dong! Ding dong! Go Go!