Your media player does not support
the subtitle format used in this episode.
The subtitles will likely not display as originally intended!
Please make sure you're using a recent version of mpv,
which can be found at https://mpv.io.
For any further questions or inquiries,
we urge you to contact us on our Discord server.
• Kaleido-subs team
Here we go!
Nailed it!
Ten out of ten!
Let's go!
That's a new record! Heck yeah!
Way to go!
Tricolore's gonna be doing a Promise today!
Looks like we're so important,
they sat us with the goats!
Thank you very much for waiting.
Master Hibiki's welcoming Promise will soon begin.
Kept you waiting, haven't we?
Bienvenue, mes chéries.
Eek! Prince Hibiki!
Prince Hibiki! We can't wait!
Amazing...
The other members are en route,
and will arrive momentarily.
Don't forget about Toriko-tori!
They forgot about me!
I just knew they would-tori!
Toriko's just so forgettable-tori!
You've found so many of the ExtraPara idols!
These are the ExtraPara goats!
It's been so long since the last time
everyone was together!
This must be a dream!
But it's not a dream!
Whoa! I've never seen Tricolore before...
They really take the cake!
Want me to introduce you after this?
Hey.
Thump!
Eep! She looked at me!
Amari?!
We're waiting for you
kimi wo matterun da yo
Open dream land!
open dream land
Every outfit you admire
akoreteru oshare ya ano daisuki
Every lyric that you love
na uta no fureezu ga
It's all inviting you to come join us
kocchi oide yo tte yonderu yo
You know that you're unique
jibun dake ga motteru no wa dare ka to chigau
There's no one else the same
tte omotteru koto
Wear that thought and you'll get a ton of likes!
ii ne ga ippai no koode da yo
Give it a twirl
kururi mawashite
And take the key to your heart
haato no kagi wo
Let's snick them, you and me
deaeta nara chakirou
And our worlds will become one
sekai ga tsunagaru
Remember the promise, shining bright
sparkling no yakusoku wo
It's gonna envelop your future
kimi no mirai to kawashita toki
Open the door in your heart
mune no oku de hiraiteiku
Go on through, 'cause your dreams are waiting for you
tobira sore ga iriguchi da yo
So come on, dive in with me
omoikitte tobikomou ne
Wear a smile like the sun and let's go to Idol Land (Yeah!)
tobikiri no egao de go to aidoru land (yeah)
We'll make it all the more vivid and lovely
kagayaki wo tsukutteikou
'Cause our dreams are shining bright!
mabushii yume de
Typesetting, TL,
timing, styling: Cynthia
Opening TL & styling: SMC-subs,
edited by Cynthia
Hibiki vs. Mario!
The BoyPara Beautification Plan!
Hibiki!
Let me introduce you to my friend!
Okay! I've gotta introduce myself properly...
N-Nice to meet you! I'm Amari... I think.
It's rice to meet you!
I'm salami and seaweed!
Agh... I totally messed that up!
You've the aura of someone
with not a shred of confidence.
Furthermore, everything you do is
completely half-baked.
Your ribbon is crooked,
and you reek of wasabi and mayonnaise.
I'd be willing to bet you don't
have many friends, if any at all.
That's what Hibiki has to say?
However, you don't use a sentence-ender,
so I suppose you can't be too terrible.
A-A compliment?!
Praise be to Hibiki!
I thought for sure she'd judge me!
Congratulations-tori!
It's an auspicious day-tori!
I... don't really think that was a compliment...
You must be tori-bbly happy! I understand-tori!
Dreamy!
Hey, hey! Listen to this for a dreaminute!
You can't dream this up! Dream it or not,
Amari's got a dreamy new manager,
and it's yours, dreamily!
Be quiet!
Hey now! Girls should be nice to each other!
I don't have time for your tomfoolery.
Hibiki, have you found any clues about PriParis?
No.
Naturally, I've searched wherever I could
for clues of its whereabouts...
...but I've yet to find anything of use.
Bon poyage, mademoiselle!
To where could it have possibly disappeared?
Long time, no see-mega!
I've got something we need to discuss-mega.
I'm sorry! I was just having a laugh—
I swear this is important!
The reason I'm here is because
I found the cause of our problem.
What?
Although we have a steady flow
of sparkling power here,
BoyPara has sent word that, for some reason,
spiny bugs have been appearing there.
That is to say, Idol Land's sparkling power
has no effect in BoyPara.
This must mean the appearance of these
spiny bugs caused the update to malfunction.
I agree.
I suppose we ought to further
investigate BoyPara's involvement.
Very well. Let's get moving.
I'll join you.
Falulu will come, too!
So will Amari and I!
What?!
I do not require your assistance.
Don't you have a Promise to do with the goats?
Please put on a sheep suit if you'd like to enter!
I shall wear no such rags.
I am Shikyouin Hibiki!
Shikyouin Hibiki!
Welcome to BoyPara!
Placing yourself above the rules as always, I see.
Nice to see you, Hibiki!
Enjoy your time in BoyPara.
Thank you.
Whoa! Freakin' rad!
I can't believe we're this close to Hibiki!
Asahi! Chill out, man!
I'm totally freakin' out, dude!
Hibiki!
I came, too!
Reona's charm is gonna give me
a serious run for my money!
Something wrong?
Oh, uh... N-Nothing! Nothing at all!
Enjoy yourself out there!
What's this? There's an empty bottle
in the burnable trash bin...
I keep telling them to dispose of
their trash in the correct bin...
Just as I suspected.
This place entirely lacks decorum.
Hey, hey, hey!
You lame-o's better look sharp,
'cuz you're all about to be my flunkeys!
LOCK'EM AWAY!
Whatever...
Not too shabby there, pal.
Heard your name's Mario?
I think the three of us are gonna get along great.
Oh yeah?
How about you join up with us?
We'll take down WITH and become
the top team in BoyPara.
You'd fit right in with us.
Name's Shinya.
And this guy's Ushimitsu.
C'mon! Bring it out!
Yes!
Understood!
This is our blood pact.
Just stamp your finger there,
and it's a done deal.
Whatever...
I must resort to harakiri!
Such disgrace.
Milord, 'tis all your lowly servant's fault.
It's come to this at last...
Unhand me!
Ushimitsu! Pull yourself together, man!
I said "unhand me"!
C'mon! It's not your dang fault!
I swear you're gonna be fine!
To meet a glorious end,
for the sake of milord. Oh my god!
Now's not the time to be reciting poetry!
Well, wasn't that exciting.
HOLD STILL!
Your laundry won't clean itself.
Make sure to do it before it piles up!
It smells like it was washed by the sun!
Looks like your boxers have a hole in them...
I'll fix that up for you!
Reona's amazing...
Spiny bugs?
Leaving Falulu and Fuwari
behind was the right choice...
Somethin' tells me there's
a girl hangin' around here...
Ah c'mon... Get over yourselves...
Meh... who cares...
A girl? No way...
Is she coming over here?
This one's...
...no ordinary person.
I can feel the darkness...
Ain't never seen a mug like yours before.
Oh? So there remain people
who've yet to hear of the Shikyouin Hibiki...
PriPara's an expansive world...
So sorry you got all gussied up for nothing.
Hey there, little princess.
My name's Mario.
I see how it is...
I'll let you in on a little something...
Soon, I'm gonna take over this whole joint,
and make this world all mine.
Isn't that a rather amusing joke...
So you think I'm joking, huh?
I can respect your ambition.
However, such ambitions require
you to actually possess such talent.
How's about I prove it to you...
...with a performance!
A performance showdown?!
Make my day.
A winning goat is a happy goat, baa baa baa!
This tired goat's about to throw
in the towel, baa baa baa...
So even goats hold Promises, huh?
Baah! No baah-ther at all!
How are we supposed
to introduce ourselves to goats?!
I wonder what Mahou-chan's up to...
You're letting us borrow the new GoatPad model?
We're live from BoyPara!
Oh, it's BoyPara!
Thanks for letting us borrow this, Ms. Goat!
This just in!
A heated performance showdown
is underway in BoyPara!
A performance showdown?
I'm your host, Meganii, assisted by...
Reona here, signing on!
First off, for the first time in BoyPara's history,
a special girls' PriPara performance-fest,
featuring a guest from GirlPara!
A show of brilliant elegance and talent!
Idol Key:
Open the stage!
This gallant style gives the impression of a knight,
and the large violet roses give off a lovely aroma.
Violet Rose Duelist Coord!
Start!
The world of this stage is a silent film
Kono sekai wa SILENT
where only the subtitles never stop
Jimaku dake tomaranai
Protecting the canary's song is my solemn duty
Kanaria no utagoe wo tasukeru sadame
I cast aside my Borsalino
BORSALINO nagesute
as roses decorate my path
Bara no chitta kono michi de
I'll fire away with a machine gun
MACHINE GUN wo uchimakure
and deceive them all, oh!
Subete wo damasou Oh
Ruined is the key to your cage;
Ori no kagi wa kowashita yo
if you still wish for your prayers to be answered,
mada kanaetai koto ga aru nara
you must take my hand and never let go.
Kono te wo nigiri kaeseba miraieigou hanasanai
Lady! She who lies shall forge her own tomorrow
LADY! Usotsuki wa tomorrow no hajimari
(Maybe!)
Your voice reaches not a single soul
Dare ni mo todokanu sono koe mo
(Bang!×5)
Lady! She who lies shall forge her own tomorrow
LADY! Usotsuki wa TOMORROW no hajimari
(Maybe!)
I know love's liar! I know love's fire!
I KNOW LIAR! I KNOW FIRE!
(Ai no)
COUNTDOWN sou kantan
A marvelous countdown
“Your song reached me!”, but is that so?
“kikoeru” tte ne
Hah! I'll recite this lie!
Hora! Usobuku yo
Cyalume change!
Left and right begin reflecting the labyrinth of mirrors
Migi mo hidari mo itsuka utsushi kagami no LABYRINTH
A paradise of my own making with no way out
Deguchi wa nai no sa marude jisaku jien no PARADISE
And yet, this song continues to resonate,
Sore demo uta wa hibiku yo
and the canary playing two roles
hitori futayaku sou kanaria wa
is not only “You”, but "Me” as well
Kimi demo ari boku demo aru no sa
Oh, lady!
She who lies shall forge her own tomorrow
Usotsuki wa TOMORROW no hajimari
(Maybe!)
Certainly this act is the truth
Enjiru koto koso shinjitsu sa
(Bang!×5)
Lady! She who lies shall forge her own tomorrow
Lady! Usotsuki wa TOMORROW no hajimari!
(Maybe!)
I know love’s liar! I know love’s fire!
I KNOW LIAR! I KNOW FIRE!
(Ai no)
I KNOW LIAR! I KNOW FIGHTER!
I know love's liar! I know love’s fighter!
(Ai no)
A marvelous countdown
Countdown sou kantan
Tomorrow is capricious
Ashita wa kimagure
(Maybe!)
Wonders are prevalent
Kiseki mo arifure
(Maybe!)
Such is why I cherish the world of this stage
Dakara sou kono sekai dakishimete
Nice!
Nice! Nice! Nice! Nice! Nice!
Not using your Making Drama
during your performance, huh?
Guess you were too busy
shakin' in your boots to do one.
You're free to think that.
Up next is uh...
Well... He's, uh...
Not really in our system just yet, but...
Relax!
Whatever. Who cares!
Lemme show ya how it's done!
I don't give a damn about your prodigy crap!
Fall into despair before the great Mario!
Woo!
I'm gonna devour the light
Hikari o kuiarase
and shoot down Heaven itself
Ten mo uchiotose
Baby, every word you speak is a lie
BABY, omaera no kuchi kara deru no wa uso bakari
Baby, does that make you jump?
BABY, tobidasanai?
Escape pod
Your words are an act,
Kotoba wa damase
exploiting everyone around!
Minna shiboritore
Your frail parachute
Hirakunai PARACHUTE
was swept up by yours, truly!
derakushite omaera no
Chocolate ice cream tornado!
Don’t bother trying! The light has
Dou demo ii! Hikari wa
been swallowed up by a pitch-black rocket!
Makkuru no ROCKET de kuiarashite
A halation of desire blooms in Hell
Yokubou no HALATION hanahirake meifu
Gimme lock!(×5)
Lock!(×7)
Now, despair!
Zetsubou
Making Dra—
Making Drama, switch on!
So you think you can just
cut into my Making Drama like that, huh?
Sapphire revolution!
Machine gun rhapsody!
Lockdown pandemic!
Stop this, you two!
You're going to hit the audience—
Listen well.
My heart...
Her heart is locked?!
Baby, every word you speak is a lie.
BABY, omaera no kuchi kara deru no wa uso bakari
I can't lock something that's
already been locked away!
My heart opens for none but Fuwari and Falulu!
Baby, did that make you jump?
BABY, tobidasanai?
Escape pod
Damn it!
Your words are an act!
Kotoba wa damase
You're exploiting everyone around!
Minna shiboritore
Cyalume Tornado!
Your frail parachute was swept up by yours, truly!
Hirakunai PARACHUTE
Chocolate ice cream tornado
Screw it! You've left me no choice!
Don’t bother trying! The light has
Dou demo ii! Hikari wa
been swallowed up by this pitch-black rocket!
Makkuru no ROCKET de kuiarashite
A halation of desire blooms in Hell
Yokubou no HALATION hanahirake meifu
Gimme lock!(×5)
Lock!(×7)
Now, despair.
Zetsubou
My heart opens for none but Fuwari and Falulu!
Mahou-chan...
We'll have a word with her about this later.
Mario's performance didn't
bring forth any sparkling power...
Meanwhile, Hibiki was able to
produce an Idol Key on her own...
I expected no less of her.
Another tornado, huh?
That's some crazy awesome power!
Both of them were astounding.
He's gone!
More spiny bugs?!
Whatever...
So even my power wasn't enough
to return them to their senses...
Just what is that fellow?
GirlPara, huh...
So that's where her little friends are...
Guess I oughta pay them a little visit.
Wahooooo!
How shall I land today?
Hm... I could do this... or I could do that!
The possibilities are endless!
Gah! Ow, ow, ow! My foot!
AAAAGGGHHHH!
What is with that annoying power?
It's all because of their sparkling power crap!
Safe! Perfect ten!
O-Oh my gosh! I am so, so sorry!
I-I didn't mean to kill you!
It was an accident, I swear!
You tellin' me that headshot wasn't on purpose?
Eeyikes! What's wrong with your face?
Oh?!
Yo, Amari!
That's a good look for you!
Eep!
Somebody heeeelp!
Come on! Aren't we friends?
Aah! Lemme go! Lemme go! Lemme go!
It's me! Don't ya remember?
No! I don't have a clue! Who the heck are you?!
No way...
This world's a silent film
Kono sekai wa SILENT
where only the subtitles never stop
Jimaku dake tomaranai
Protecting the canary's song is my solemn duty
Kanaria no utagoe wa tasukeru sadame
I cast aside my Borsalino
Borsalino nagesute
as roses decorate my path
Bara no chitta kono michi de
I'll fire away with a machine gun,
MACHINE GUN wo uchimakure
and deceive them all, oh!
subete wo damasou Oh
Ruined is the key to your cage;
Ori no kagi wa kowashita yo
if you still wish for your prayers to be answered,
Mada kanaetai koto ga aru nara
you must take my hand and never let go!
Kono te wo nigiri kaeseba miraieigou hanasanai
Lady! She who lies shall forge her own tomorrow!
LADY! Usotsuki wa TOMORROW no hajimari
(Maybe!)
Your voice reaches not a single soul
Dare ni mo todokanu sono koe mo
(Bang!×5)
Lady! She who lies shall forge her own tomorrow!
LADY! Usotsuki wa TOMORROW no hajimari
(Maybe!)
I know love's liar! I know love's fire!
I KNOW LIAR! I KNOW FIRE!
(Ai no)
A marvelous countdown
COUNTDOWN sou kantan
"Your song reached me!", but is that so?
"Kikoeru" tte ne
Hah! I'll recite this lie for you!
hora usobukuyo
Lady! She who lies shall forge her own tomorrow
LADY! Usotsuki wa TOMORROW no hajimari
(Maybe!)
I know love's liar! I know love's FIRE!
I KNOW LIAR! I KNOW FIRE!
(Ai no)
I KNOW LIAR! I KNOW FIGHTER!
I know love's liar! I know love's fighter!
(Ai no)
A marvelous countdown
COUNTDOWN sou kantan
Tomorrow is a caprice
Ashita wa kimagure
(Maybe!)
Wonders are prevalent
Kiseki mo arifure
(Maybe!)
Such is why I cherish the world of this stage
Dakara kono sekai dakishimete