All right! We swept the Autumn Idol Grand Prix!
And that means tomorrow's the celebration concert!
That's the power of the unstoppable Dorothy!
And for that celebration concert...
Yeah!
You can count me out.
What?
Open that hidden door
himitsu no tobira wo akeyou
There's no need to be shy – within lies the wonderland of your dreams
hazukashigaranaide soko wa suteki na wandaarando
I wanna bring about a world all of my own
dare mo ga mita koto nai you na
Like nothing you've ever seen
watashi dake no sekai meikingu shiyou
Go on and bring all your friends
tomodachi mitsukete sasottara
This passport connects all lands and crosses all borders
sore wa unmei no suteeji he
It leads you to your destined stage
tsunagaru (tsuzuku) saikou no pasupooto
Let's go!
let's go
Dreams are made to come through, so seize that chance
yume wa kanaeru mono chansu ni tsunageyou
You can be the idol you've always dreamed of being
akogareteiru aidoru mezashite
We can all bring about a miracle together
minna de issho ni kiseki okosou yo
That shining, radiant
kirakira kagayakidasu
PriPara Fantasy
puripara fantajii
What's a Mega Genius-panda?
But why?
It's to celebrate our victory!
You remember Mister Genius and his promise...
to take our Autumn Dream Parade Coords at the celebration concert?
I will attain your Autumn Coords when next we meet.
He's not satisfied with the Summer Coords; he wants the Autumn ones too!
Stuff that.
Well, okay...
But if he does show up, we can just take the Summer Coords back!
Yeah, but last time time he blew right past our defences.
Are the PriPara police really up to the task?
Of course they are!
Right, Ajimi-sensei?
I'd say naught-Da Vinci.
You heard her. I'm out.
Aw, come on...
The concert's that big a deal to you?
You're that anxious to show off...
in front of Reona and the others who didn't win?
Really?
Mirei, Sophie and Aroma haven't won at all, you know?
See?
Mikan, you don't want to bum Aroma out either, right?
I like singing.
But not if it makes Aroma sad.
It's kind of a cosmic shame...
We may have to give it a miss this time.
Capisce...
We didn't win the Grand Prix this time either...
True, even though Lala and Dorothy have won two apiece...
We haven't even won one.
But...
I'm sure we will next time!
Enter.
Excuse me.
I'm here to deliver the student council logbook.
Very good.
Acting deputy...
Do you find yourself captivated by your reflection?
Every day.
What of it?
Oh, I just...
was thinking of how the
Phantom Thief Genius was a narcissist.
Good day, acting deputy.
I wasn't expecting...
That a team containing Houjou Sophie and Toudou Shion both,
those two eminent genii, could possibly lose a Grand Prix.
Just who held them back, I wonder?
"Those without talent can close the gap with effort"?
How callow.
They should stand back and allow genii to flourish.
I... have lessons to attend to.
One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven, eight!
It's pri unusual to see you training alone.
One, two, three, four!
Five, six, seven...
The loss took the pri out of your sails?
My spirits are as high and unhallowed as ever.
But the sin of being unable to lead the peons to victory falls upon me!
Since when were you the pri-eader?
Regardless, we need but amass
magical power and pool our efforts...
and the path the hell shall be illuminated.
Hearing the devil talk about effort-pri...
D–Did I here some blasphemy pass those lips?
Besides, you're always blathering about how necessary lessons are!
We're in step for once, it seems-pri.
Wanna practice together?
As long as you don't trip me up.
That's my line-pri.
Go for it, you two-kuma!
One, two, three, four!
Just who held them back, I wonder?
I'm home!
Onee-chan!
Our whole class is going to watch the celebration concert!
You'd better make sure you don't make me look bad!
It's been called off.
Huh?
The Phantom Thief's just gonna come and take our coords anyway. What's the point?
Onee-chan...
Onee-chan, you're so...
Spineless!
Me and all my friends...
we don't have a PriTicket yet; we can't even go to PriPara!
So we look forward to watching on TV and cheering for you!
I thought you were so cool,
being in such an amazing competition!
I was thinking about maybe even...
even congratulating you...
Non...
How could you give up just because of some stupid phantom thief?
Onee-chan, you dumb, spineless jerk – I hate you!
Non!
Lala-chan!
Eiko-chan?
We'll be cheering you on at tomorrow's celebration concert!
See you then!
You want to do it again now?
There are girls who don't have PriTickets...
and others who want to cheer us on!
They're looking forward it!
How can idol not perform because they're afraid of some phantom thief?
Yeah, and when he steals our coords, what then?
And you agreed it'd be hard doing it in front of Mirei and the others, too.
W–Well, yeah...
Mirei? That outfit's your...
idol prosecutor coord?
You're still at school?
We're all ready over here.
Huh?
Please allow me to check your belongings-panda.
I hope they can arrest him.
Mm, but he's totally my type...
Go, phantom thief!
You're clean-glo. Next!
The security they've set up is out of the cosmos.
Is this all for the celebration concert?
You bet it is.
Mirei, Shion!
We'll be assisting with the security as well.
The phantom thief won't escape the long arm of the law.
I shall whet my blade upon him!
Not that you can sharpen a wooden shinai.
You can perform without fear.
The policeman's soul inside me is getting Munch, Edvar-ed up!
It's been piqued and my excitement's at a peak-asso!
Da Vinci.
Ponkan's gonna catch the phantom thief!
So I have to make my super secret preparations –
I've gotta run-oire!
No one thought we'd call it off at all.
We've gotta do our best too!
Yep, yep!
All right, I get it.
For cryin' out loud...
There's no point if I don't sing anyway, is there?
Our opponent appears and disappears like smoke.
We can't assume we have him barred like this.
Phantom Thief Genius – come at me any time!
You don't have to try to pick a fight.
Go?
I've never heard such restrained words from you.
Per... Perhaps...
Don't worry about a thing!
The PriPara Nurses are here as well!
PriPara Nurses?
We should have nurses on standby in case anyone gets hurt.
I can take care of anything to do with medicinal plants.
Yodel-le-ea-fu!
This herb treats constipation and fever.
I usually apply a jellyfish, though...
Doesn't it sting you?
I'm wouldn't trust them to treat any injuries.
True...
And all the while...
Where am I? Who am I?
I can't think of a plan to catch the phantom thief at all-Da Vinci...
And the concert's about to start!
Da-Da-Da Vinci! Da-Da-Da Vinci!
I've figured out how to Turner...
the tables on the Phantom Thief, G-Mark my words!
Ajimi's figured out how to Turner the tables
on the Phantom Thief, G-Mark her words!
Da Vinci!
Thank you for waiting, everyone.
The winning team of the Autumn Dream Idol Grand Prix,
Cosmic Omurice Da Vinci, will now perform their celebration concert!
The word "love" is written with ketchup on the omelet rice.
And the coord expresses the same love!
Omurice Ketchup Coord!
Da Vinci!
And "smile" is written on the mayonnaise-and-roe sauce.
Doesn't it just bring a smile to your face?
Omurice Mayo Roe Coord!
Geru!
Herbs are fried in butter within the frypan.
Nothing in the universe compares to this cooking show!
Delicious Chef Coord!
Cosmo!
Yay!
Blink and you'll miss it!
Da Vinci, everyone!
Cosmic Omurice Da Vinci is invincible!
Dream Theatre Concert, switch on!
Come on into the kitchen
saa ikou kicchin
You're gonna be the head chef!
shuyaku wa mochiron kimi sa
O-O-Omelette rice
o-o-omurice
O-O-Omelette rice (Yummy!)
o-o-omurice (yummy)
O-O-Omelette rice
o-o-omurice
De-De-Delicious (Tasty!)
de-de-delicious (oishii)
O-O-Omelette rice
o-o-omurice
O-O-Omelette rice (Woohoo!)
o-o-omurice (fu fu)
O-O-Omelette rice
o-o-omurice
Ooh, delicious!
ooh delicious
Crack open a lovely round egg
manmaru tamago o watte
Crack it!
watte
Beat it in a bowl
booru ni iretara mazemaze
Beat it!
mazemaze
And add a splash of milk
miruku wo shoushou iremashou
Add it! (Woohoo!)
iremashou (fu fu)
The secret to the fluffiest creamy eggs
fuwatoru tamago no hiketsu wa
What is it?
naani
Get a dollop of tasty butter
oishii bataa o hitokake
Slather it!
nurinuri
Light a fire under the frypan
furaipan ni hi wo tsukeyou
Hee-haa!
hi-ha
A cute little onion
tamanegi-chan
A cute little mushroom
mushroom-chan
Throw 'em all together!
minna de issho ni nacchaou
A cute little chicken
chicken-chan
A cute little capsicum
piiman-chan
But I don't want any green peas
green peas dake wa no
No!
Everyone has worries sometimes
no
fuan wa dare demo aru
But you've gotta keep your head high
demo tachimukawanakya
Add rice to the egg and stir it up
tamago o irete raisu to daikaiten
Mix it, mix it... Flip!
kurukuru pon
Omelette rice, omelette rice
omurice omurice
Om-Om-Omelette rice
omu-omu-omurice
Write your true feelings in ketchup
kechappu de kaita honto no kimochi
Delicious! Delicious!
delicious delicious
Airy Change!
Deli-Deli-Delicious!
deli-deli-delicious
Let's dig in now to our omelette rice
itadakimasu masu omuraisu
Just one mouthful
hitokuchi dake de
Cyalume Airy!
Will fill you with happiness
shiawase hazumu
Cyalume Airy!
The spotlight shines on you
supottoraito ni terasarete
You'll surely become
kitto kimi wa
The idol you've dreamed of
risou no aidoru
And bring a smile to everyone
minna egao ni shichau
Thank you all!
Now what's the password?
aikotoba say
We're cosmically grateful!
Omelette rice, omelette rice
omurice omurice
Tension max!
Om-Om-Omelette rice
omu-omu-omurice
Isn't it fun?
Write your true feelings in ketchup
kechappu de kaita honto no kimochi
Delicious! Delicious!
delicious delicious
Deli-Deli-Delicious!
deli-deli-delicious
Mm, that omelette rice was the best!
gochisousama sama omuraisu
Om-Om-Omelette rice, om-om-omelette rice
o-o-omurice o-o-omurice
Ring the bell of everyone's dreams!
Om-Om-Omelette rice
o-o-omurice
Everyone's dreams become one!
Resound, Charm Bell!
Thankies!
Thank you!
It's over already?
That's not what they usually do...
And the Phantom Thief never showed...
I wanted to see him...
Is it over now?
Everyone! I want to say-nt Peter's Basilica: thank-ubrick! Thank-ubism!
Thank you, everyone!
We love you!
Thank you cosmically!
We switcheded our clothes!
I see!
That was their plan!
No phantom thief's getting his hands on these!
This plan is Ponkan's pièce de Renaissance!
Nothing's happening?
Well done, everyone.
A truly splendid performance.
Meganii!
Thank you!
And the coords are safe and sound, too.
Let's get them to a secure place right away.
I'll take care of them.
Sure thing-Da Vinci!
Well done, everyone.
A truly splendid performance.
Meganii?
Thank you!
There are two Meganiis?
They look the same-same!
He's multiplying!
Cosmic!
How shock-limt-Da Vinci!
So he's...
shown himself at last!
I am the real Meganii. That one is a fake.
No, I am the real Meganii. That one is the fake.
You certainly are persistent.
Stylish!
Tough!
Guy!
How's that?
You won't defeat me.
Stylish!
Tough!
Guy!
Not bad at all.
I must compliment you as well.
Will you take this seriously?
I cosmically can't tell them apart.
Does that mean they're both real?
Um, so...
It's gotta be that one!
That one-Da Vinci.
It's cosmically him.
That one, I knows it!
Okay, this one!
No, he's–
When the wings which soar...
in the sky are spread...
A sole lilium casa blanca shall bloom in the darkness!
My name is Phantom Thief Genius!
Phantom Thief Genius!
I believe I sent an advance notice:
I will take the coords at the celebration concert.
Indeed, and so we waited for you!
We won't let you get away!
And you think you can do that by aping my methods?
Let us find out!
Go get him, Meganii-san!
Go for it, Meganii!
Don't let him beat you, Phantom!
Oh no!
Do take care, my dear.
To commemorate our meeting.
Oh, Lord Genius!
To you foolish idols, endlessly repeating your pretense of friendship...
Farewell!
He's gone.
No way...
He stole them again?
It's okay-Da Vinci!
The real Autumn Coords...
didn't art nouveau anywhere-Da Vinci!
What? How?
Before the show began, Meganii, Ham-senpai and I...
prepared some fakes ahead of time!
So the coords the phantom stole...
Were the fakes-Da Vinci!
All right!
Way to go, Ajimi-sensei!
I knew we could leave it to the PriPara Police!
Not bad!
Not at all!
Say, I can't seem to find Rina-chan anywhere.
Phantom Thief Genius?
Your schemes have proven an amusing diversion.
Thank you for your cooperation, milady.
Rina-chan!
I have attained the true Autumn Coords.
Now the curtain falls!
He got us!
After him!
That jerk!
Get back here!
You won't outrun me!
Ponkan's going Renoir-fter him too!
Please stay calm, everyone.
Hologrammation!
We're tracking his movements.
The power's not restored yet-panda?
How strange-panda!
I'm looking into it-panda!
Well done-panda.
Hey, he's not here-panda.
But we should have trapped him here-panda.
Very strange-panda.
A tracking device.
He's stopped.
He's on 4-F.
Let's go!
No, wait.
That's not...
I'm starved-panda.
Where'd that phantom thief get to-panda?
It's in front of the bamboo grass vending machine.
He seems to have picked up on our trick.
So if he's trying to lead us above...
He's below!
Everyone, head to the basement!
Phantom Thief Genius!
Why are you doing these mean things?
I will bring revolution to PriPara.
What revolution?
There's no use telling you.
Tell me what it is!
A type of sugar cube.
You're lying!
Yes, I am.
I won't let you get away with this!
We're gonna catch you and take our coords back!
I welcome you to try – if you can.
You're not getting away!
Lala!
The phantom?
Yeah!
This way's a shortcut!
The power's...
back on.
He read our moves!
What?
But he should have taken this one!
He's disappeared again...
Meganii-san!
If our coords keep getting stolen, then the Parade...
Don't worry.
It will be held as scheduled.
Let's see if the system will reprint the stolen coords.
We won't let the phantom do as he pleases.
We will capture him without fail!
Onee-chan!
Non!
We saw your show!
The coords were stolen, but you really gave it your all!
Congratulations!
Make sure you catch the phantom sometime, too!
Thanks and capisce!
I'm not...
gonna give up!
minna de warattara
kitto niji ga kakaru yo
When we all smile together, I'm sure a rainbow will connect us
doremifa sora ni rainbow melody♪
tsukuro! saikou no stage♪
Sing do-re-mi above the clouds and make a rainbow melody
te wo tsunaide kureta kara ne + issho ni ite kureta kara ne
It's because you took my hand, and it's because you're here for me
dakara dekitanda yo = mirakuru na dorama ga! (Yeah!)
That we were able to make this marvellous drama (Yeah!)
nachuraru ni hibiki aeru
egaichaeba kasanarunda ne
Our voices in unison – take a brush and the strokes blend naturally
sore wa kiseki mitai na harmony
Our beautiful harmony is miraculous
puripara! utattara minna tomodachi da yo ne
PriPara! Let our voices free, and we'll all be friends
suteki na sumairu no anata wo mattetanda yo!
I've waited to see your brilliant smile!
hora mite! utattara melody, niji ni naru kara
Now try it: our melody becomes a rainbow
watashitachi no sora wo kazatte suteeji ni shiyou
Adorning our own sky; now, come on and sing
kokoro kirakira, rainbow melody♪
yume wa kanau yo!
The rainbow melody shining in our hearts makes our dreams come true
Next Episode
Long time no scare, everyone!
Ah! It's a ghost!
I'm not a ghost! I'm Ran-tan!
Take a clo-scare look!
Ca–Capisce!
Have a Good Fright
And a Happy Halloween!
Next time, Have a Good Fright and a Happy Halloween!.