Hey, I'm back to my real-world self.
Where is this place?
I know! They sell hamburgers here!
Hm?
Prism Stone?
What's going on?
himitsu no tobira wo akeyou
hazukashigaranaide soko wa suteki na wandaarando
dare mo ga mita koto nai you na
watashi dake no sekai meikingu shiyou
tomodachi mitsukete sasottara
sore wa unmei no suteeji he
tsunagaru (tsuzuku) saikou no pasupooto
let's go
yume wa kanaeru mono chansu ni tsunageyou
akogareteiru aidoru mezashite
minna de issho ni kiseki okosou yo
kirakira kagayakidasu
puripara fantajii
Her Debut Date
Wait, what? I don't get it.
Why can we see Prism Stone from here?
The answer should go without saying.
It means we're outside PriPara right now.
So that's why our Coords disappeared?
That would be it.
What?
Pushu...
Sophy!
But it's closed! And I really wanna eat a hamburger!
It's a revelation that you yearn for more than meat buns.
Here you go.
Thankies!
That reminds me: during the Summer Grand Prix...
What was Andou doing there?
Phantom Thief Genius! There's no use hiding-Da Vinci!
I'll arrest you through and th-Ruvens, just watch me-chelangelo-Da Vinci!
There's nothing here.
Devi? So he was aware we had invaded his sanctuary.
Hey...
That's the headmistress' hair.
It certainly is.
Hey, we're in there too!
Hi there!
So who's recording us, then?
A purple butterfly...
It was a spy camera?
That granted him twenty-four hour surveillance of PriPara.
Yes, and he invaded the system and
PriPara itself using this computer.
That emblem...
It's Hibiki's.
What?
The evidence has been gathered.
Phantom Thief Genius is Shikyouin Hibiki!
The acting headmaster?
That Shikyouin?
Yeah, I can see that.
How shock-limt!
One good Turner deserves another!
Shikyouin Hibiki must be arrested-Da Vinci!
So it's true...
Fuwari!
What's that?
You've discovered the thief's identity?
Laala and the others just contacted us-kuma!
They said it's Shikyouin Hibiki!
What?
You mean the movie star famous outside PriPara?
He's also the acting headmaster at Paprika Academy!
How many more minutes until we reach PriPara?
Fifteen minutes if we hurry.
Eleven if we really hurry!
Please really hurry!
Roger!
We need to get there quickly...
If we hurry...
What is his goal, anyway?
This is turning into something bad-kuma.
If he comes back, we're gonna catch him-panda!
Pan!
How are things over there-usa?
We're all ready to ambush him-Da Vinci!
He's bound to come this way if we just wait for him.
C'mon, PriPara Police!
Capisce!
Yep!
I can't believe the phantom thief
would turn out to be Hibiki...
I feel like I know less about him than ever.
There he is!
He's coming this way!
Um... what was it...
"The star of justice shines in my heart!"
He's going past.
What?
Why's he going into Prism Stone?
I don't understand!
How shock-limt Egon Schiele!
Come on, after him!
It won't open!
Where's the exit?
Over here?
It's locked from the outside!
Hey...
Isn't that...
Shikyouin Hibiki?
Why's he in PriPara?
Welcome to PriPara!
Is this your first visit to PriPara?
I suppose so.
He's a guy, right?
I'll take your ticket, please.
Certainly.
There we go.
I'll now determine your brand with the Fashion Scope.
Be my guest.
The brand suited to you...
Is... say, this is...
The as-yet unworn brand...
For the nobles among all nobles,
said to befit only the utmost nobility...
Brilliant Prince!
I can't believe it!
And now your registration is complete.
Thank you.
May we meet at the dawn of the PriPara revolution.
A toast to your good fortune.
The Brilliant Prince Cyalume Coord.
The long velour coat expresses true luxury!
And the shining crown accessory embodies a heroic prince!
Isn't that...
It couldn't be...
Prince Hibiki?
A news bulletin.
A bearer of the legendary Noble brand
has appeared in PriPara at last.
That brand: Brilliant Prince!
The bearer: Hibiki!
He looks a fine man-nekon.
Shikyouin Hibiki is in PriPara?
A man in PriPara-panda!
Shikyouin's in PriPara-kuma!
We're well awar-uvens!
Arrest him!
Here.
Are boys allowed in now?
That must be it!
Prince Hibiki!
Go!
I'd like to enter, please.
Your manager?
No manager necessary.
How novel!
Okay, just a moment.
He's managed to enter PriPara;
the system's protocols must have been overwritten.
Did he use Hologrammation?
Or did the stars simply align?
Break a leg.
Well, then – I'll see you at the performance.
Okay!
Prince Hibiki!
I'm so glad boys are allowed in now!
This excitement is unbelievable.
Keep going-Da Vinci!
Prince Hibiki!
My prince!
When the wings which soar in the sky are spread...
A sole lilium casa blanca shall bloom in the darkness!
My name... is Phantom Thief Genius!
But why?
Where's Prince Hibiki?
No way!
Why's he in his Phantom Thief outfit?
I've appeared to reveal my true form.
Shikyouin Hibiki – pleased to meet you.
There he is! Prince Hibiki!
So...
Huh?
Which means...
Indeed.
For my noble aim, I have played the role of this phantom thief.
What?
He's spilling it!
Quickly! We have to take him to
the PriPara HQ for judgement!
Arrest him-panda!
What?
The phantom thief was Shikyouin Hibiki?
Come off it, now!
Oh, my prince! You're too much!
Show us that historic boy's performance!
Oh, and I should add....
I'm a girl.
What?
What was that?
Surely not...
Should I repeat myself?
I'm a girl.
My birth certificate.
Wha-at?
Wha-a-at?
Mister magician?
A... girl...
My whole world view is shattered-glo!
Fuwari! Fuwari! Are you okay-tori?
We have to get to a hospital!
Let's Gauguin! We have to Picasso up our feet
and catch this Tarou Oka-most heinous criminal!
I can't.
What?
I was born to protect idols.
If Hibiki is a female,
she hasn't stolen in, but entered as a legitimate idol.
What?
Hmph.
Well, then.
Listen well now to the message of she, who stands at last...
upon the stage of her beloved PriPara.
Prince Hibiki!
Show us what you've got!
You there, within your powerful yet weak-willed heart,
kimi hakanaku mo tsuyoi
Find yourself spurred by revolution
sono kokoro ni ima kakumei nosetara
You there, heed now the future
kimi tomadowazu furuu
assured by my unerring nobility
seigi no naka ni aru mirai wo goran
Leave the past behind
kako wo wasurete
Unsuited to lipstick or ladylike apparel
doresu mo ruuju mo kanawanai
I am a perfect knight of beauty
rinjin mo kamigami mo urayamu
Envied by god and mortal alike
perfect beauty knight
Pure amore love - let it bloom ever magnificently
pure amore ai sakihokore utsukushii
A casablanca bursting open like raging magma
hana akaku takeru maguma kasaburanka ni
Amore, come here, I shall tell you now the truth
amore iza shinjitsu wo oshieyou
What is “love”?
ai suru to wa
Love is merely a fantasy for fools
oroka na shoudou
Yet it is by the love's whims that we two
shikashi bokura wa ai ga yue ni
Have been drawn here
koko ni iru
Making Drama, switch on!
Onward!
I will uphold it!
Sapphire revolution!
Pristine frenzy!
The wheels of revolution will not turn without sacrifice!
Now come here
oide
Airy Change!
Pure Amore Love - An eternally unfading bloom;
pure amore ai eien ni kawaranai
Gold Airy!
A casablanca with its thorns wrapped around your heart,
hana toge wo matotta mune no kasaburanka
She's produced an Airy Change
outside the Dream Theatre?!
Amore, ah! Avert not your eyes from the flower;
amore aa akai yori mo akai hana
its hue rivaling any shade of crimson
katsumoku se yo
This pristine frenzy is for you
junshin ranbu for you
Indeed, it's for the sake of love and these dreams
sou ai ga yue yume ga tame ni
That "I" am here
boku wa aru
Prince Hibiki!
She's amazing!
My prince!
How did she pull off her Noble Gold Airy like that?
She simply seized the hearts and minds of the audience.
Incredible.
It was really amazing.
An overwhelming performance.
Amazing...
That was incredible!
Wonderful!
I can't believe we heard such an amazing star sing!
Everyone loved your song so much. They're still standing.
Hearing it from you, Princess Falulu, is the greatest honor.
You're the mage I met back then, aren't you?
I am.
Because you wished upon a star.
Yes, I'm really glad I met you again.
But...
Do you dislike my true face?
No, it's wonderful.
But...
Hey, why can't we get in-kuma?
You're the one who called us here-pri!
And even if you hadn't,
we've got a bone to pick with you-usa!
Lautr-et us in!
Let's Gauguin!
Gigi, are you okay?
"Gigi"?
I'll call you that from now on!
You're not barred from entering.
Your entrance is this way.
Please enter through here.
I'm gonna be firs-Titian!
A Meganee in black-kuma?
I've never seen one before-usa.
What's going on-pri?
You don't think-nekon...
Sentence-Ender Room
Hey! What's big idea-pri?
This room has been prepared separately
due to Hibiki's weakness against sentence enders.
What's that? It's easel to get in on sentence enders!
Just rememb-randt:
you can do anything you set your mind to!
Pri!
Mirei!
Let me out-pri! I'm ap-pri-ealing you here!
Pri has a pri-oud and illustrious pedi-pri, you know...
Why have you done this?
Let them out!
If I did, this exchange would be a futile prospect.
Exchange?
Hey, my Dream Tickets!
Falulu, why are you here?
Hibiki's a bad person, you know!
That's not true, Laala.
Huh?
Falulu's going to join Gigi's team.
I thought so...
"Gigi"...
C'mon, Gigi, gimme my Dream Tickets back.
So you manipulated the system after all.
I suppose I did.
But only to a minor degree.
I want to discuss this calmly.
Why did you steal our Dream Tickets?
I want to compete with you in the
Winter Dream Idol Grand Prix...
with these Dream Tickets on the line.
What?
I guarantee, more than anyone else here,
I love PriPara.
There's no way that's true! I really, really love PriPara!
You said it, Laala-pri!
Yep!
That's right!
PriPara and Aroma are really important to me!
Don't underestimate us!
Then I want to prove just whose love is greater.
Were I to say that alone,
who would have reason to compete?
That's why I took your Dream Tickets.
When you were being all thief-y...
"These Dream Tickets do not befit you."
You totally said that!
Of course, that is true as well.
Compared to my love, yours is simply vacuous.
What does vacuous mean?
It means an empty expression, with no depth or pri-fundity!
We've got to the point in a somewhat roundabout fashion,
but let us do battle – me with a
prodigy team befitting my own ideals,
and you in a team formed according to your ideals.
Surely the stronger love will win through.
'Scuse me for a moment here,
but aren't you a high schooler?
Don't you feel a little embarrassed,
challenging us middle schoolers and primary schoolers?
Should I hold back, then?
If I win, I will reform PriPara.
What?
The Saints...
It's the Saints...
Our erstwhile Divine Idols.
Their era was unsurpassed.
Only those whose greatness was
acknowledged by all stood upon the stage.
And yet in the current PriPara,
there exists not a single Divine Idol.
It's an assembly of rank amateurs, after all.
I want to restore PriPara to its golden age.
Pri-pri-pri!
So what if we're amateurs?
We're all friends! We're all idols!
That's what's so great about PriPara!
We all do our best to rank up!
That's what makes PriPara great!
We'll become Divine Idols, just you wait!
You say that, but not a one of you ranked up
before I intervened, did you?
My word.
Is there even a point in competing with you, I wonder?
You should give them back, Gigi.
You should give everyone their
Dream Tickets back if you took them.
These tickets are like an idol's body itself.
Falulu should know. Her body is made of PriTickets.
Princess Falulu...
What are you saying?
Then all of my preparations will be for...
Please.
Then how about this?
You oversee your academy's rules.
Your parents are a prosecutor and a lawyer.
And you're respected by all.
No one will object to your judgements,
myself included.
No objections!
I should tell you, my love for PriPara loses to none either!
And just how will you demonstrate that?
Had you ranked up recently? I can't recall.
I present my judgment!
You can spout all the sophisms
about love you like, but a sin is a sin!
They shall not be overlooked.
Shikyouin Hibiki, return the stolen Dream Tickets!
All right!
Encore! Encore!
Prince Hibiki!
Come back again!
My prince!
Please perform again!
And what will we do about the game?
Miss Minami Mirei, who hasn't won a single Grand Prix.
Shall we not determine who is correct?
Mirei!
You can bet we'll accept!
We'll postpone your arrest until we've won!
No objections!
Capisce!
Hmph.
Encore! Encore!
Understood.
Come to mama, my little Dream Tickets!
Were you lonely without your mama?
Thanks, Falulu!
That reminds me,
I've yet to receive my Cyalume Charm.
This golden charm...
with a shining crown emblem, is most suited
to a Noble idol such as you.
The Military Look Coord for the ivory knight alighted in PriPara.
The gallant short jacket and golden frills
about the waist are simply splendid!
You there, within your powerful yet weak-willed heart,
kimi hakanaku mo tsuyoi
Find yourself spurred by revolution
sono kokoro ni ima kakumei nosetara
You there, heed now the future
kimi tomadowazu furuu
assured by my unerring nobility
seigi no naka ni aru mirai wo goran
Leave the past behind
kako wo wasurete
Unsuited to lipstick or ladylike apparel
doresu mo ruuju mo kanawanai
I am a perfect knight of beauty
rinjin mo kamigami mo urayamu
Envied by god and mortal alike
perfect beauty knight
Pure amore love - let it bloom ever magnificently
pure amore ai sakihokore utsukushii
A casablanca bursting open like raging magma
hana akaku takeru maguma kasaburanka ni
Amore, come here — I shall tell you now the truth
amore iza shinjitsu wo oshieyou
What is “love”?
ai suru to wa
Love is merely a fantasy for fools
oroka na shoudou
Yet it is by the love's whims that we two
shikashi bokura wa ai ga yue ni
have been drawn here
koko ni iru
Next Episode
Hibiki...
Why do you dress up as a boy?
Are you curious?
Then why don't you act opposite me today?
You want... me to act with you?
Shikyouin Hibiki's
Splendid Everyday Life
Next time, Shikyouin Hibiki's Splendid Everyday Life.