Is Falulu here yet?
I can't wait to hear about her time at PriParis,
the capital of flowers and fashion-pri!
I'm sure she's grown a bit.
But I'm still max ticked off!
That stupid Phantom Thief Genius.
He made a fool of us by stealing our coord
and calling our friendship fake.
It's the worst-pri!
Yeah.
Oh well.
Falulu and Unicorn are finally coming back to see us!
Let's just relax and have fun today.
It's been so long since I've seen Almighty Unicorn
that I'm getting excited-kuma!
When she turned into Pegasus,
she became a Legendary Mascot-usa!
With that, there's no way we could disrespect her-kuma!
That divine light...
Almighty Unicorn!
Your light is so radiant, Almighty Unicorn!
Long time no see.
Huh? You're back to normal-kuma?
I turned back after two days.
Okay! You can get off now, Falulu.
Oh, and watch your step.
Falulu!
Hi, Laala, girls!
It's been too long!
We're finally together again!
Yeah! And you all seem to be doing well.
So do you!
Since you're back, here's my
extremely happy capisce!
Capisce! Capisce!
Capisce! Capisce! Capisce! Capisce!
Whaaat?!
Falulu Has Returned
Falulu Has Returned.
Welcome back, Falulu!
Nice to see you again, Non.
Being able to talk with my beloved
Falulu again is like a dream come true!
But Non, I thought you were a Fuwari fan now.
I have a separate place in my heart for Falulu.
I bought you a gift, Non.
They're flower seeds from PriParis.
Really?
Thank you so much!
I'll make sure they grow nicely!
We bought stylish PriParis
souvenirs for the rest of you, too.
PriParis cookies!
A pendant-pri!
It's so cute!
This is pretty stylish!
Thank you very much.
You even got a Go table!
Um, what about us?
Did you get anything-usa?
We got special presents for the two of you.
Hooray-usa!
Your generosity is much appreciated-kuma!
I'm sure it's a wonderful item for an exceedingly
handsome gentleman such as myself-usa.
What?
Huh?
It seems they're so impressed they're speechless.
It's wonderful that they like them!
It looks like the two of you are still really close.
Of course.
But I am also a capable manager.
We're trying to achieve her dream of being a Divine Idol,
so there are still times when I have to scold her.
Falulu knows...
Come on, Falulu!
Redo that move!
No, that wasn't harsh enough.
I need to be stricter!
No! Do it over!
Unicorn has secretly been practicing scolding.
No! Don't tell them that!
More importantly...
Unicorn's tail looks like spiral poop!
Spiral poop!
Why you!
If you don't shut your traps, you're gonna get it!
Um, now that we're on the topic,
just who are these little girls-pri?
These Mini-Falulus are all the same as Falulu.
Wait, that means...
The PriTickets that don't have owners?
Exactly.
I now have the job of visiting the other PriParas
and collecting dropped PriTickets.
And then...
These girls are born from the feelings of girls who wanted to become idols.
They are awoken as Vocal Dolls just like Falulu.
Falulu also helps me with it.
Falu!
Falulu!
So they're all Falulu's little sisters.
They're all so cute!
But aren't there a bit too many-pri?
What's "-pri"?
Huh?
What is it?
"-Pri" is... uh...
A verbal quirk-pri.
What's a verbal quirk?
What is it? What is it?
Verbal quirks like "-pri" and "-chanko"
are usually used at the end of a sentence...
to portray a type of character or atmosphere.
What's "atmosphere"?
What is it? What is it?
"Atmosphere" is... "Atmosphere" is...
What you roll rice balls in!
Wrong-pri!
If you use "-pri", you can become a pop idol like Mirei.
Now then, everyone practice it together.
And start!
Pri! Pri! Pri!
One more time.
And start!
Pri! Pri! Pri!
I've memorised "-pri"-pri
I've memorised it-pri.
Good job, everyone.
Pri...
They really learned it-pri.
Everyone playing with Falulu, gather around the horn.
Okay!
Stop that!
Hey, that's—
No, not there!
Falulu really is acting like a proper older sister.
Falulu.
It's almost time.
Oh, whoops.
I'm sorry.
I have to go to a PriTicket snapping event for my fans.
Aww...
We can play more once I get back.
Please look after them.
Capisce!
Now then, those playing with Unicorn gather round the horn.
Ouch...
Hey, you cant just go wherever you want!
What the heck are you doing, you brats?!
What should we do?
They're in groups!
They're doing whatever they want.
Let's split up and catch them-pri!
Got it.
Mini-Falulus, where are you?!
Hey, it's Laala!
Laala, give me your autograph!
C-Capisce!
Your autograph!
Autograph it.
Maalulu memorized her autograph.
Naaruru also memorized it!
Hyaruru too!
Charuru too!
They're pretty good...
My calculations say they should be around here-pri.
Dressing rooms are over here!
Found them-pri!
Oh my.
Wow!
Chanko, that's really good!
It's perfect!
Thank you-chanko.
Now give us an even more daring, mature pose!
Shy-chanko.
But now I...
have climbed the stairs of adulthood-chanko!
Chalu!
Hey, get out of the way-chanko!
A swarm has been found!
Prepare yourselves!
Get back here!
It looks like I'll just be eternally innocent-chanko.
O Sole, O Sole Mio.
Malu!
Maalu!
Faalulu!
Chalulu!
Canzone!
Wha?!
Falu.
Pianissimo.
Glo!
Glo! Glo! Glo!
Oh, it's tuna.
Pushuu...
I'll just take a little break.
I'm so happy to meet you, Falulu!
Thanks you!
Even if you're in PriParis, I'll always be your fan!
Thank you!
I wonder if they're staying put
and behaving themselves.
Wait! Please stop!
Hold it!
We said stop!
Hello!
We're Pink Actress!
Kyupikon!
All right, here we go!
Music...
Yeah!
Kyupikon!
Huh?
Stop!
You're not getting away-pri!
Hey, you, stop!
Falu!
Woo hoo!
Hooray!
Wee!
You're not getting away-pri!
Hey, stop!
W-What's with those little girls?
They broke the stage!
Maaruru memorized kyupikon.
Kyupikon!
W-What do we do?!
We can't perform like this.
At a time like this, there's one thing to do...
Kyupikon!
Kyupikon! Kyupikon!
Girls, calm down-pri!
Those brats are at tension max!
Relax!
Unprecedented!
This is absurd!
This has become a disaster.
I'll take responsibility and snap off my horn.
Forgive me!
Kyupikon!
What should we do?
What's wrong?
Hey, wait!
Huh?
Falulu!
We're in trouble!
No one was in the room.
Falulu's been looking all over for you.
As you can see, they're causing trouble for everyone-pri.
Hey! Cut it out!
It doesn't look like any of them have noticed you yet.
Stop!
I just came up with a great idea!
Huh?
Those who want to see Falulu's concert,
gather around the horn!
Falu?
Huh?
I'd also like to see you perform since it's been so long.
Me too.
Us too!
Kyupikon!
You can do it, Falulu.
Got it.
Hooray!
We'll show you how much brighter she'ch become since PriParis.
Please scan the appropriate number of My Tickets for your coord.
Coord Change Start!
A mauve arrangement full of high-end cloth as pure white as an angel.
"Mauve" is what one in Prance would call purple.
Angelic Mauve Coord!
Falu!
It's been a while, everyone!
I've wanted to see you all again!
Falulu!
We've been waiting!
Good luck!
Making Drama Switch On!
Hop!
For all of you!
Tick Tock Flower!
Cyalume Change!
Falu!
Thank you!
Falulu received pink.
Lovely.
Are the wings gold because it's from PriParis?
She's ranked up from Major Class's Popular Idol to...
...Widely Famous Idol!
Falulu started in the Understudy Class at PriParis.
Maalulu wants to be an idol just like Falulu.
So does Naaruru!
Pyaruru too!
Charuru too!
We love Falulu!
Falulu loves all of you, too.
So even they can be cute when they're like this.
Even though they just caused so much chaos,
they're growing up fast and are desperate to perform concerts.
Falulu's concert really was something-pri!
You've improved so much since you've been at PriParis.
Yeah.
We'll work even harder now!
Pri!
Yeah.
Same!
Huh?
Why's that one all by herself?
You're right.
What's wrong?
Gaaruru...
Huh?
Isn't that Falulu's Non?
Gaaruru!
Capisce!
She bit ya!
Let's see here.
Gaaruru!
Dorothy!
It's pointless.
Falulu and the other girls were all born
when feelings of becoming idols came together.
But Gaaruru is different.
Huh?
Even though girls normally strive to be sparkling idols,
it doesn't always go that way.
I can't sing.
I'm a horrible dancer!
I never want to do or see any more concerts!
Maybe l'm not meant to be an idol...
They couldn't achieve their dreams.
Those girls' feelings of hopelessness gathered together...
And that's how Gaaruru was born.
Gaaruru...
She said she hates idols...
Sophy, you can understand her-pri?
Gaaruru!
She said she wants to be a monster...
Gaaruru...
It went by so quickly, but you really helped us!
Thank you.
Did all of you learn a lot?
Yeah!
All right, now start!
Capisce-pri-kyupikon!
Good job!
That's all?
All right, get on up there,
Maaruru,
Naaruru,
Charuru,
Pyaruru...
They could have stayed longer...
Unicorn has her own work to attend to, so there's no helping it-pri.
But we'll see each other soon, right?
99...
Huh?
We're missing one!
Eh?!
Our flight bound for PriParis will be taking off shortly.
Oh no!
Gaaruru's not onboard!
Eh?! Gaaruru's not?!
Gaaruru ran away?
Why?
I wonder if there's something she doesn't like.
She's bitten a lot of people!
We have to find her quickly.
I may not have much energy,
but I'll do everything I can.
Gaaruru!
Gaaruru's in the system control room!?
Don't do that!
We're coming!
Wait for us, Gaaruru.
Next time:
It's Sunny Once In A While.
Gaaruru!
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!