Special announcement!
Shikyouin Hibiki,
the distinguished son of the Paprika Group,
came in from EuroPara yesterday.
While studying in EuroPara,
he flourished as both a movie star and model.
Many of his titles have been sold out,
making him a legendary artist.
I hope he stays here forever.
It's Shikyouin Hibiki!
The one from TV?!
Really? The movie star?!
W-Why's he coming to Paprika Academy?!
Hibiki!
Huh?
What's going on?
I love you, Prince Hibiki!
Please marry me!
Prince Hibiki!
Mr. Shikyouin!
Look over here!
H-i-b-i-k-i-T-V!
Prince Hibiki, you're so beautiful!
You're mesmerizing!
He's pretty cool, huh, Reona?
Yeah!
Looks like he's rich, too.
And probably smart as well.
White, yet black. Even better.
My prince...
What?!
He's your prince?!
But why's he at our school?
My prince!
P-Prin...
Prince...
We've been awaiting your arrival,
Mr. Shikyouin Hibiki.
It has been far too long, Madame Gloria.
My, what a greeting! How fitting of a Europrian prince!
Isn't that right, my sweet Rina?
Right-puru!
It's an honor to be here.
My Prince and the Blue Bird of Misfortune.
Students of Paprika Academy,
I have an important announcement to make today.
Starting today, Shikyouin Hibiki,
the distinguished son of the Paprika Group,
will be attending our high school for one year.
Hooray!
Although Hibiki has spent most of his time in EuroPara,
he is the grandchild of the academy's chairman.
Oh, I see...
As such, he has been given the
position of acting headmaster.
Go, Rina!
Amazing!
Acting headmaster?
Really?!
I didn't see this coming.
Me either.
Why?
Headmistress Ookanda, isn't it kinda weird for
a high schooler be the acting headmaster?
Dorothy...
Definitely not!
That's because...
...he won the Monsieur Handsome Universe Prince
of the Year contest...
...with his exquisite heart, technique,
and physique expected of the ideal male,
and has been crowned the ideal prince by
the queen of the three Plutoniean countries.
Since he's the ideal prince,
our job will be to spend a whole year like a prince!
That means we get to ride in a horse-drawn carriage.
I can't wait!
This will be awesome!
Now then, everyone,
let's follow Hibiki's example and be pure, righteous,
and beautiful Paprika Academy students.
I look forward to making all of your acquaintances.
We can't wait!
What are you doing, Fuwari?
He didn't even notice me.
He forgot all about me.
What's the big idea?!
Hey, what was that for?!
I'm sorry.
Oh, uh...
You don't need to cry.
Was it something I said?
No.
Fuwari...
Eh?!
So, you became PriPara's princess scholarship
student because Shikyouin asked you to?
Yes.
But when you went to speak to him again,
he didn't acknowledge you.
Speaking of him, what'd he say when you two first met?
When I met him?
I was playing with Yukino the goat
and the other animals in the Palps like I always did.
Hello there.
Would you like to sing with me?
All animals are friends.
Come on, let's sing together.
Maxie.
You have a lovely voice.
For Maxie to be drawn to someone other than me...
You must have a pure heart.
Not at all.
Maxie suddenly ran off while I was
letting him get a drink from the river.
Perhaps he was drawn to your voice.
I've never seen him run that fast.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to.
No sentence-ender.
If you're looking for somewhere to rest your horse,
there's a place on the other side of that road.
What's your name?
Huh?
It's Fuwari.
Midorikaze Fuwari.
Fuwari...
Your song was beautiful.
It seems I've finally found what I've been looking for.
Huh?
My princess.
Wow! How romantic!
If I was there, he would've said that to me!
How wonderful.
It's the season of Koi.
love
But that looks like a Tai.
While he's right that Midorikaze's singing is beautiful,
I wonder if the reason his heart was cleansed
was her lack of a sentence ender?
What?
Does that bother you, President Minami?
Of course not!
Prez's pri is wonderful the way it is-bri.
And then what?!
And then...
Since I've been chosen as the ideal prince,
I've been searching for someone to be the ideal princess.
A princess?
Right.
So please, become my princess.
And to do that, I would like you to go
to the PriPara on Parajuku street.
You see, I believe PriPara will bring forth the ideal girl.
I said that, and asked her to come here.
I see.
So by first winning the Summer Idol Dream Grand Prix,
she'll be on her way to becoming the Princess of Summer.
Correct.
I'm sure she'll shine brighter than
anyone else if we polish her.
I hear you've had a profound admiration
for PriPara for quite some time, Ms. Gloria.
So please give Fuwari your
utmost guidance and encouragement.
Of course!
So that's why you came all the way to Paprika Academy.
But it seems my prince forgot all about me.
What? You're burying your PriTicket?!
If you do that, the ghost of wasting will come for you.
But...
Your collar... pushuu...
What's this?
Looks like it's from your prince.
Really?!
Fuwari, I was so busy I couldn't talk to you today.
But once you've become an elegant princess,
I'll come sweep you off your feet.
Hibiki.
Oh, my prince! I will!
I'll put my everything into
becoming an elegant princess!
Isn't that great, Fuwari?
Yeah! I can't wait to perform!
The world is so beautiful.
Wow. She really does have a lovely voice.
Indeed.
Time to be quick and decisive.
I'll have to act fast and ask her to join Dressing Pafé's Dream Team.
I'm sorry, but since we still can't find a brand for Fuwari,
she can't have her debut concert yet.
What?!
What's with that?!
Isn't everyone in PriPara an idol?!
I'm cosmically sorry!
I'm buried under a teracosmic pile of work.
But I'll do my super best to make something soon!
Thank you.
I'll leave it to you.
Cosmic capisce!
What's a manager?
You really don't know anything, do you?
Please allow me to explain-usa.
T-T-Tori!
Are you okay?
T-T-T—
Fuwari.
This is Dressing Pafé's manager, Usagi.
Mr. Usagi?
Usa!
A manager is a must-have for every idol here in PriPara.
You could say their importance is akin to that of air-usa.
Well, animals wouldn't be able to live without air.
So a manager is truly important.
T-T—
I feel refreshed-kuma.
Yeah! Yeah!
Is everyone as excited as I am-usa?
Ack! What's that?!
There's a visible silhouette around it!
Who's that bird?
That's Toriko-kuma.
Toriko?
Kuma...
And since she's drowning in misfortune,
they've started calling her the Blue Bird of Misfortune.
Th-The Blue Bird of Misfortune?!
Usa...
Misfortune seems to follow her wherever she goes-usa.
But...
Because of that, everyone avoids her which means she's always alone-usa.
So it's best not to associate with her-usa.
But every animal is a friend.
Toriko, let's become friends, too.
Tori...
I won't be able to understand you
if all you say is "toriko".
Toriko can speak normally-tori.
Toriko only brings misfortune to those around her-tori!
Wait!
I'd like to try talking to Toriko.
Ah, Fuwari!
Toriko!
She flew off in this direction.
Ah, over there!
Eh?!
Huh? Where?
Who knows.
She must have hawk eyes.
Toriko!
Lightning out of nowhere?!
This sure is some strange weather...
You okay?
Porapora...
Don't worry, I'm fine.
Ouch!
Washbin lightning?
We're really having some strange weather...
Are you okay?!
See!
I told you that Toriko brings misfortune to those that go near her-tori!
Don't worry, I'm hardheaded.
Did you come here with the thought of eating Toriko?
Making grilled bird out of me-tori?!
I'm sure you'd like it with sauce and salt-tori!
No.
I want to be friends.
You say you want to be friends,
but as soon as I let my guard down,
you'll end up making fried bird out of me!
Wow. She is always thinking negatively.
Happy-go-lucky!
I believe if you laugh and have fun,
happiness will follow.
Yeah.
Laugh, you say?
That's quite a dark laugh you have there...
Dorothy...
That's right, Toriko is Toriko.
Living alone in the darkness suits Toriko the best-tori.
Ah, wait!
Toriko!
Please wait up!
Tori?
Tori?!
Like Toriko said-tori.
Misfortune falls upon those who come near her-tori.
Ack, she's floating away-tori!
G-Grab ahold of this-tori!
Thanks.
Tori!
I'm sorry.
Toriko can't swim-tori!
Farewell.
May this Toriko of Misfortune be released from
her calamity, and become a star up in the sky.
Are you okay?
You shouldn't have-tori.
You should have left Toriko behind-tori.
Otherwise more misfortune will befall you-tori.
That won't happen.
They're coming-tori!
The demons of misfortune have come to take us away-tori!
Just who are demons of misfortune?!
Come on!
Blue Bird of Misfortune really does suit you!
But thanks to this,
I've been able to get closer to you, Toriko.
Why-tori?!
Why won't you leave Toriko alone-tori?!
That's because every animal is a friend.
Since we both got soaked in the same river,
we're already friends.
You really... won't come to hate Toriko?
I won't.
Are you sure you want to be friends with Toriko?
Absolutely.
Even if misfortune befalls you?
That won't happen.
I've decided-tori!
Toriko will be your manager-tori!
I'm Midorikaze Fuwari.
I look forward to working with you.
Same here-tori.
Fuwari...
Let me give you your PriPass-tori.
With this, you've become a PriPara idol-tori!
That thing's ancient! Does it even work?
Well, Toriko's never been a manager before...
Actually, it would be better if you didn't—
Thank you, Toriko.
Tori!
And this case is closed peacefully!
Yep!
Yeah.
Tori!
Please scan the appropriate number of My Tickets for your coord.
You can also scan each other's Friend Tickets.
Coord Change Start!
Thank you for waiting.
It's finally time for everyone to see Dressing Pafé's ninja coord!
Nin! Nin!
In The Water Coord!
Go!
Even though they're ninjas, they want to stand out!
They're going against the grain and using vibrant colours!
Nin! Nin!
In the Woods Coord!
Yeah!
And let's dance with a fluttering scarf completely covered in hearts!
Nin! Nin!
In the Fire Coord!
Making Drama Switch On!
Drums!
Guitar!
Bass!
Stereo in full blast! 2:3 Rock!
Let's Go!
Cyalume Change!
Go!
The three of them shine so brightly.
It really gets me excited!
Thanks!
Way to Go!
Thanks for everything today.
I just can't wait to debut!
Then let's snap!
I don't have any more PriTickets.
I did it with Laala yesterday.
What?!
You shouldn't snap your PriTicket with them!
We're looking forward to your debut, Fuwari!
You would've been much better off snapping with us.
Yeah.
Thanks.
I guess you'll be waiting too, Toriko.
I've never heard of an idol without a brand-tori.
Toriko really is the Bird of Misfortune-tori!
Sweet dreams, my prince.
Goodnight, Toriko.
Fuwari, your princess training looks intense.
But I'll do my best.
I want to live up to Hibiki's expectations.
Big news!
The new brand we've been waiting for has finally been finished!
That means you can finally have your concert!
Yeah.
I want to stand on stage as soon as I can!
Toriko's so excited that her heart might stop beating!
Toriko'll be grilled bird soon-tori!
Next time:
Fuwari dances! Her first concert-tori!
Aim for your dreams!
Let's go PriPara!