Who's there?
Just what are you doing?
Identify yourself, villain!
Flittering from the sky above...
And appearing in utmost black!
A sole margeurite...
Fuwari?
Appearing for one night only... the Ma...ma...
Um... what was it?
Mustard... Mascot night?
Oh, and I spent so much time practicing...
Do you, perhaps, mean to say "Masquerade Time"?
The appellation I have adopted: Phantom Thief Natural!
Halt!
Just what do you intend?
What is your intention riding Maxi, Fuwari?
Return to me, Maxi!
Maxi! Do you not recall who is your mistress?
That's right. Return to me.
Now you obey. If only you'd done so from the start.
Just what are you doing, Fuwari?
I have come to steal away...
The sorrow and anger within your heart!
Koe mo kibou mo kasanete
Hyaku paasento no sumairu
toki ga tomaru kurai no hikari hanate we are one
(we are one)
bacchiri! kyou mo minna kawaiku ne!
ippo agareba hirogaru sorezore no suteeji
pittari! kyou mo minna tsunagatteru
onaji yume miteryu koso yuuki ni naru yo
ochikondari jishin nakunaru toki mo aru kero
te to to tsunagi namida wo futtobashichae
koe mo kibou mo kasanete
hyaku paasento no sumairu
toki ga tomaru kurai no hikari hanate we are one (we are one)
tokimeki zettai mitsukeyou
minna kokyuu wo awasete
koko kara ippo susumeba
kimi to puripara we are one
(We are one)
A Pop and a Step and a Pri-Pri-Pri!
What is the meaning of this?
You have opposed my machinations from the very start.
And even now...
I face torture in choosing a fifth member.
Yet you still seek to further impede me!
The fruits of my thievery.
Won't you become my friend?
Preposterous!
This Friend Ticket is immortal.
Facing rain, wind and snow...
It shall remain, undaunted!
It's been swept away!
Mere detritus.
As flimsy and ephemeral as you, yourself.
Enter the Phantom Thief Spineless Chicken!
Of course you discard your Friend Ticket!
How can you be so heartless?
Begone!
How about we call it quits here...
...you shameless imitation Phantom Thief?
Alas! I've proven to be the
Blue Bird of Unhappiness after all-tori!
Surely my mere presence
brings you pain and suffering-tori!
Toriko is only fit to dwell among the foulest insects-tori!
That's not true!
Toriko, you're the Bird of Happiness!
I won't suffer anymore!
We'll all find happiness!
Li'l Curly!
You won't escape me again!
Prenoir-pare to be befriended-Da Vinci!
I get a Kiki out of you as always, Li'l Curly!
Our battle reaches a Correggio-scendo!
Da-Da-Da Vinci! Da-Da-Da Vinci!
Feast your eyes on this-Da Vinci!
And plop!
I ain't jo-Courbet-in'!
Knock, knock, knock-Kongourishiki!
Initialising the Hologrammation system!
Oh, no!
A landslide victory! Bravo, Brueghel!
Wait, Li'l Curly!
Man, SubPara is bearitably full of holes and leaks!
It's raining cats and dogs.
I recommend all of you equip this.
He looks as stylish in goggles as any other glasses.
This rain feels almost...
like Hibiki's lamentations.
I guess if you went through that...
you might lose faith in your friends-pri.
One's heart could become as bare as Bald Mountain.
Impotent deploration,
truly unbearable.
I think Hibiki's a good person, deep down.
Are you kidding me?
If she's good, that makes me
even more perfect than I already am!
Maybe that's why Falulu...
What are you doing, Falulu?
Hibiki's a bad person you know!
That's not true, Laala.
In a way, Lady Shikyouin Hibiki is quite...
straightforward.
She's not shy about telling us she's a genius.
She catered to us fully.
Flying together was a ton of fun!
You don't mean... that supercilious attitude
was to spur us to greater heights?
Surely not.
I guarantee, more than anyone else here,
I love PriPara.
But, you know...
I can't just declare her the enemy.
That voice...
Mr. Andou?
I've kept mum to Master Hibiki...
but I must...
There is something I must tell you.
Oh, but...
If I do, it will mean a total betrayal of her!
No, but if I don't speak...
But on the other hand!
Would you just spit it out already?
The truth is... Master Hibiki...
wants to become a Vocal Doll, just like Lady Falulu.
Just where did Andou go?
Surely he hasn't become engrossed in some puddle.
Hibiki!
What do you lot want?
We have to talk to you-pri!
She won't listen to anything with verbal quirks!
I apologize for my rudeness.
Do you really want to become a Vocal Doll?
You can't do that-pr–
Why would you abandon the real world?
Have you taken leave of your senses?
I understand how you idolize Vocal Dolls...
Let's go flying again!
I don't think you should do it.
You should think things through-kuma!
Whom did you hear this from?
Andou?
You've betrayed me!
I am deeply sorry.
However...
Consider yourself dismissed!
You can live henceforth as a masterless goat!
Master Hibiki...
I understand.
You're casting aside even Mr. Andou-pri.
Andou is but a mere hired hand.
What do I owe him, or he me?
You've gotta let your true feelings show, Gigi!
You might even win back Fuwari!
If you seek to impede me,
you'll be let loose just like Andou!
Do your worst!
You are barred from PriPara!
Hibiki, wait!
You know...
I had no idea what you were going through!
But if it were me...
Even if I were in your position...
I would hold faith!
I'd believe in my friends, even if they let me down!
Well, I don't.
Hup!
Hold on!
If that's how you wanna play it,
I'll turn your revolution back around-pr—
I won't let you back out of it-pr–!
If one of us attains the rank of Top Idol,
you'll acknowledge FriendAll as a rival anew,
and let us compete in the Spring Idol Grand Prix-pr–!
Certainly – when that day comes.
One! Two! Pri! Pri!
Mirei, you contemptible fool –
there's no way you can become a Top Idol.
One! Two! Pri! Pri!
No one even goes to SubPara. No matter
how many likes you get, it's meaningless!
One! Two! Pri! Pri!
If giving 301% won't cut it...
I'll ramp it up to 55301% this time-pri?
55301%?
"Go, go, Mirei"!
That's right!
After that, we'll sweep the Spring Idol Grand Prix...
and bring Hibiki's self-flagelating vocal doll
ambitions to an end-pri!
Hey, yeah!
But... can we win?
We don't have another choice.
All right!
Go, go, Mirei!
Go, go...
... so they listen to this music
minna ni todoke kono music
Just get on the stage (on the stage) and you're an idol too (idol too)
suteeji agareba (agareba) dare datte aidoru (aidoru)
Let's get better every day
joushoushikou de ikou
Hop step jumping!!
hoppu suteppu janpin!!
Even when you mess up, and get a bit down
shippai shitari chotto hekondemo
We're all friends
minna tomodachi
Let's make a sparkling Making Drama together
kirakira na meikingu dorama isshoni tsukurou
PriPara paradise polish your heart
puripara paradaisu haato migaite
Miss Hibiki has ranked up to Serious Idol!
A world where dreams come true
yume wo kanaeru sekai
Let's grow our idol ranks
aidoruranku wo agechaou
Prince Hibiki is amazing!
Prince Hibiki has this in the bag!
There's no point even competing!
A shining paradise always every day
kirameki paradaisu donna toki mo
Let's keep our smiles going
egao tayasazu ikou
A little effort will change the future
chiisana doryoku ga mirai wo chenji
Let's start!
hajimeyou
Mirei!
Thank you-pri.
To Gaaruru... to all of you.
Right now... I'm pri darn happy!
Please scan the appropriate number
of My Tickets for your coord.
Starting the Coord Change!
Sprinkling love and courage about,
in the marching band style.
The vivid colors effuse energy!
Blue Sky March Coord!
Pri!
Hey, you guys!
I'm the pop idol Mirei!
With a pop and a step and I've gotcha!
Go, go, Mirei!
It's because you've all been there for me
that I can shine infinitely!
It's because you've all cheered for me...
That I'm gonna keep on sparkling
brighter and brighter-pri!
Get ready for Mirei's happy-lucky pri-pri power!
Curses! At this rate, I won't even be able to listen.
Pretty!
muite mo
From every angle, you're pretty
muite mo puritii
You know it's true
puri puritii
Go and be
migoto
The best idol that I know you can be
no aidoru puri miseru puri
Pri-pri
puri puri
Those words will cheer you up
genki deru kotoba
It's the best!
sapuri yori
I'll show you now – let's do it together
oshiete ageru saa issho ni
Pucker those lips, like you're about to kiss
kuchibiru wo kisu no katachi sutanbai
And from there
soshitara
Take both hands
hoppe wo
Pri!
puri
And press your cheeks
ryoute de
Pri!
puri
And take a deep, deep breath!
gyutto shite shinkokyuu
Here we go!
iku yo
Pu-pu-pu
pu pu pu
Pri-pri-pri
puri puri puri
It'll pri-ng you closer to your dreams
yume wo migaku puri
You just need to look this way
shisen watashi dake ni choudai
We'll pri-dge the chasm, no matter how wide
koko ni puri puri
Pu-pu-pu
pu pu pu
Up, up and up we go!
appu appuri
You can't get pri-nough!
oboreru hodo puri
The purest,
toretate
Yes!
hai
And prettiest heart
puritto na haato
It's inside you, and it's pri perfect
todokeru yo puri paafekuto
Pri!
Making Drama, switch on!
You know it's the cutest, pri!
ichiban kyuuto na puri
You know it's the greatest, pri!
ichiban saikou na puri
Show me that smile
itsudemo happii
Fresh Sweets Park!
Don't keep it pri-vate – show the world!
purimaite miseru
purimaite miseru cyalume
Airy Change!
Be pri-born as a greater idol still!
atarashii aidoru miseru
Pu-pu-pu
pu pu pu
Pri-pri-pri
pri pri pri
It'll pri-ng you closer to your dreams
yume wo migaku pri
Gold Airy!
You just need to look this way
shisen watashi dake ni choudai
Amazing!
We'll pri-dge the chasm, no matter how wide
koko ni puri puri
Mirei!
Way to go!
Pu-pu-pu
pu pu pu
Gigi, look at Mirei!
You know you can't
hoka no hito ni
Hide your true self away
purai kinshi puri
Gold... Airy?
Just stand tall
shinsen
All right!
yoi
You don't have to be shy
purittona sumairu
Your purest heart is pri perfect
tobishichau puri paafekuto
Thank you so much, everyone!
Pri-pu, Pri-pu
puri pu puri pu
Pri pri-pri
purii puri puri
We're pri darn perfect-pri!
puri pu puri paafekuto puri
Pri!
Miss Mirei, what a phenomenal occurrence!
You've ranked up to Top Idol!
Mirei!
Mirei... Mirei!
Congratulations, Mirei.
I can't hold back the waterworks-kuma!
Your performance was so great,
it's reduced me to a blubbering wreck-kuma!
I'm so unbearably proud of you!
Gigi!
I can see it...
Clear as day, I can see it.
The Head Disciplinarian, fresh from her
greatest performance ever, is here in front of my eyes...
Pardon my intrusion.
I am here to report that I have become a Top Idol.
Therefore, please allow us to enter the
Spring Dream Idol Grand Prix as discussed.
What more fitting gift than poppies for a Pop idol?
Poppies are my favourite...
I couldn't imagine you'd really reach the rank of Top Idol.
Especially as you're restricted to the SubPara systems.
I am nothing if not capable of recognizing
effort where such recognition is due.
You mean you heard my performance?
Er... yes...
Thank you!
We'll hold a rematch as discussed.
That said, you're sorely mistaken
if you think you can defeat me.
What do you mean?
Welcome to CelePara's Prince Hour!
Today I have a joyous announcement for all and sundry.
In this Spring Dream Idol Grand Prix,
both CelePara Revue and FriendAll
will hold a rematch with the Spring Coord on the line.
However, I have made an amendment to the rules.
The idol who successfully rings the bell
will become the Princess of the Four Seasons.
Say what?
The members of the Princess of the Four Seasons' team...
shall automatically become a Princess Team...
This team can enter the PriPara Dream Parade.
And further to this, the one who, by ringing the Charm Bell,
receives the miracle of their wish being granted is the Princess of Four Seasons alone.
Have I made myself understood?
Essentially, the Spring Dream Idol
Grand Prix is both a team competition
and the arbiter of the one who stands at the apex of PriPara.
An individual event?
If we want to stop Hibiki's wish from coming true,
we have to win this event.
I want to help Hibiki.
And... if I become the Princess of Four Seasons...
Impossible. That's because I'm the one–
Don't kid yourself! Ol' Dorothy's got this one in the bag!
A demon's power is infinite!
I wanna eat all the seasonal fruits at once with Aroma!
I have to become the Princess of Four Seasons!
Yep!
I'm giving it my all.
What should I do?
I don't want to let anything sad happen...
...in the PriPara I love so much!
Please look forward to the Spring Dream Idol Grand Prix.
She's continuing to twist the rules
according to her own whims.
I can only hope this doesn't place
undue stress on the system.
Falulu, what do you think?
I mean, about how Hibiki said she wants to become a Vocal Doll.
It made Falulu happy.
It did?
It's lonely, being myself every night.
Falulu is sure she'll have lots of fun with Gigi.
Falulu can't be with you at night.
Say, Sophy...
What did you feel, seeing Mirei achieve a Gold Airy?
Unlike we in our CelePara ivory towers,
Mirei reached that supreme stage in the dilapidated SubPara
through blood, sweat and tears alone.
The sense of defeat resounds through me.
I wasn't there for Mirei...
when she toiled under the yoke of Hibiki's tyranny.
I wonder if I placed myself higher than my friends.
Salutations.
Have you tired of the water fountain?
Hibiki!
I have a matter to discuss with you.
I cordially invite you to join CelePara Revue, Reona.
saizensen de shikakaeru batoru  seifuku ni kigaemashou
kyou wa chotto senobishite
meikuappu shichaimasho
kakattekite yo  makeru wake ni wa ikanai no
(Wow Wow)
sensenfukoku  kikoeta desho
"matta!" wa nashi ne
Here and Now
misete ageru  kimi no haato  neraiuchi
kirari teritorii
kimi wa koko made haittekoreru kana
No way, no way, no way!
There's no way you can join that strumpet Hibiki's team!
Hold on, Dorothy! You see...
You're staying right by my side, Reona.
No one else can have you!
Revenge of Celebrity 4
Next time, Revenge of Celebrity 4.
Seriously? Those guys again?