ikuyo tomodachi no tomodachi wa love
Let's go, friends of friends are love
heart ni kuttsuku takaramono
A treasure in your heart
donna koto datte
Whatever happens
change kawaru yo happy
We'll change it into happiness
afuredasu friend style
Friend Style going wild
issho ni itai na kimochi ii
Spending time together is so fun
datte kimi wa fuwa fuwa na ofuton mitai
You're like a fluffy futon for the soul
chanto homete tataete sa
You tell me how great you think I am
ano ne arigatou terechau kedo
Embarrassing, but thanks anyway
nande darou nanika shite agetai
Not sure why, I always want to help you out
itsu datte
Every time
mukaiai kisoiaetara ne
And facing you in a contest
motto ii na
Would be great
sonde tomochike pakirou
So let's snap Friend Tickets
iroiro dakedo kono kimochi otome no pure
Many different emotions, all straight from a maiden's heart
mune no hiki itai na namida mo jibun
No point in denying your tears
atsu atsu yuujou drier
The burning hot friendship drier
atete massugu ni
Will blow them all away
kira kira no heart da
Leave your heart all a-sparkle
minna ni deata kara hora
Since meeting you all
konna ni tanoshii
It's been so fun
konna ni ureshii
I'm so happy
special na
So special
Don't try to hide your tears
namida wo fuke
misete yo
Take a look
daisuki da yo no smile
The "I love you" smile!
ikuyo tomodachi no tomodachi wa love
Let's go, friends of friends are love
heart ni kuttsuku takaramono
A treasure in your heart
donna koto datte kaerou yo happy
Whatever happens we'll change it into happiness
unmei datte omoeru yo
Call it destiny, whatever
konna ni tanoshii
It's fun either way
konna ni ureshii
I'm so happy
special na kankei da mon
Our relationship is so special
agetai
Here it comes
daisuki da yo no smile
The "I love you" smile
watashitachi ga best my friend
We really are the best of friends
odoridasu friend world
Dancing in our friend world
iru kara daijoubu
With you, I'll be fine
tomodachi ga zutto iru kara
We'll always be friends, forever