My heart flutters to the rhythm of this magic ornamentation
and I feel myself coming to life
Love, dates, everything's always the same old story
But tonight, I simply wish to dance once more
My heart comes alight like raging fire
An throbbing passion unable to be extinguished
Let this flower rooted inside my heart bloom
I'll shine brighter than ever before
I'll bloom exquisitely with the fire lit inside of me
Just like the red flowers of passion
The flowers of my dream come into bloom with splendor
If these flower petals ever wither,
They'll return as buds once again
Just like those from the red passion flowers